‪THE LOVE LAB
‪Can the women briefly gather around?
‪-Don't you want to go out with someone?
‪-Tell me.
‪My head hurts.
‪Wait. She's fainting.
‪Just tell me.
‪-You can tell me anytime.
‪-I told you earlier.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Kyung-ho?
‪-What?
‪Who's my first choice?
‪No, it's Jung-min.
‪He's the person
‪you want to talk to the most?
‪-Jung-min?
‪-Yeah.
‪NODDING
‪Really? I thought you guys
‪talked a lot already.
‪Well…
‪You see…
‪-Wait.
‪-Okay, got it.
‪-Don't we have to go to bed?
‪-Yeah.
‪The only person
‪I am attracted to romantically
‪is Jung-min.
‪But the person who is interesting,
‪funny, and draws my attention
‪-is Kyung-ho.
‪-Okay.
‪But I don't think it is
‪a romantic interest.
‪But you do want to get to know him, right?
‪-You have to get to know him.
‪-Even if I did,
‪my feelings for Jung-min are quite strong.
‪So she has a romantic interest
‪in one person,
‪but the other person is
‪just interesting and funny?
‪Isn't that a romantic interest too?
‪…are quite strong.
‪-So I don't think my feelings will change.
‪-Really?
‪-But it would be nice if we could chat.
‪-Right.
‪Honestly, I don't think it's just me.
‪-I'm sure everyone feels the same way.
‪-Yeah.
‪We all have our first choice,
‪but there could also be
‪a second choice, right?
‪But since we only have five days,
‪and that is too short,
‪-it would be nice to have that chance.
‪-I agree.
‪You see, if we don't create opportunities,
‪we may think certain people
‪are already a done deal
‪and not even give it a try.
‪That's why I think it would be
‪a good idea to create opportunities.
‪That's all you're wearing?
‪It's cold outside.
‪Put some clothes on.
‪Come and tuck me in, then.
‪I'll think about it.
‪Do you feel pretty certain
‪about Do-geon?
‪-Me?
‪-Yeah.
‪-My feelings for him?
‪I mean, how both of you feel. I'm curious.
‪-Right now, Do-geon is my first choice.
‪-Okay.
‪What if there's no one
‪I want to go on a date with tomorrow?
‪-If I don't want to go on a date…
‪-Why? Did it not go well with Kyung-ho?
‪Did it not go well with Kyung-ho?
‪It's not that it didn't go well.
‪I don't think we really…
‪-You both didn't feel much?
‪-You don't feel sure about it?
‪-Really?
‪-You seemed certain about each other.
‪-I know. Really?
‪He is my first choice,
‪but he's not sure.
‪-Kyung-ho told you that?
‪-He said it himself?
‪NODDING
‪He wants to get to know everyone
‪or something like that?
‪Yeah, he said it's too fast.
‪-Too fast?
‪I mean, it's too soon
‪for him to decide anything.
‪Oh, it's too soon.
‪So he doesn't want
‪to make a decision
‪-about anyone yet?
‪-But…
‪-But I kind of get it.
‪-Yeah.
‪It has only been one day.
‪-Do you have a second choice?
‪-Me?
‪I think she does.
‪I think I know who it is.
‪I don't know. Tell me.
‪I think I know
‪both of you guys' second choices.
‪Who is it?
‪I think it's Jung-min for the both of you.
‪-Who?
‪-What?
‪-Jung-min.
‪-No.
‪-Jeez.
‪-If it isn't him,
‪good for me.
‪Come over here, Ga-yeon.
‪-Good for me!
‪-It was
‪a highly strategic move to find out.
‪-You wanted to see our reaction.
‪-This is how it's done.
‪-Gosh, that threw me off.
‪-But who's your second choice?
‪-Who's yours?
‪-I don't have one.
‪You don't?
‪Actually,
‪everyone else is much older than me
‪except for Do-geon,
‪-so there's no point.
‪-I get your point.
‪If I were to choose a second choice…
‪Yeah, who is it?
‪-Kyung-ho?
‪-Who is it?
‪Jung…
‪JUNG WHO
‪Honestly, it's Kyung-ho.
‪-I knew it.
‪-I thought so.
‪It isn't Jung-min.
‪Wait, it's Kyung-ho?
‪What's up with that reaction?
‪Are you okay?
‪Come on, child.
‪-Child!
‪-What's wrong?
‪Man, I had no clue.
‪Why? Was it totally unexpected?
‪Yeah. You said you already knew him…
‪Oh, maybe that's why
‪you are attracted to him?
‪I didn't sense anything between you two.
‪There's nothing.
‪-Is it because he seems fun?
‪-Just curious?
‪-If I must choose. He's fun to be around.
‪-Okay, I get it.
‪I'm going to leave now.555
‪This is nice.
‪-Aren't you cold?
‪-I'm okay.
‪So is there a reason why you chose me?
‪It was an interesting choice
‪to make in that situation.
‪Oh, is that all?
‪I did want to
‪have a conversation with you.
‪Oh, when?
‪When did you get that thought?
‪-Well, since yesterday?
‪-Really?
‪For me…
‪I don't know if I should say it.
‪You were my first impression pick.
‪Really?
‪I did not expect that at all
‪because I felt like Ga-yeon and I
‪had no connection whatsoever.
‪I wondered why
‪I'm her first impression pick.
‪You see, for my first impression pick,
‪I chose you
‪because you seemed mature to me.
‪I was intrigued by you,
‪but after I actually chose you,
‪I realized we didn't really click.
‪And you also seemed
‪pretty certain about your choice too.
‪So even though I chose you at first,
‪it didn't lead anywhere.
‪But I did want to get
‪a chance to talk to you.
‪I felt like everybody has someone
‪they want to get to know
‪but is hesitant.
‪Everyone seems pretty set
‪about who they like.
‪But I think that can change.
‪It could change.
‪You never know.
‪Yeah, we still have two more days.
‪-I've been talking with Chae-rin a lot.
‪-Yeah.
‪She must have someone she is interested in
‪besides me too, right?
‪But if we keep going like this,
‪we won't get a chance
‪to chat with someone else
‪we're interested in, even a little bit.
‪I thought that'd be a shame too.
‪-I think
‪-Yeah?
‪Ga-yeon only has eyes for Jung-min.
‪-Really?
‪-No.
‪She kept saying she wants
‪to get to know someone else.
‪-Right.
‪-That's totally Kyung-ho.
‪She created this whole thing
‪to have a chat with Kyung-ho.
‪She created this whole thing,
‪but she made it sound like
‪she's certain about Jung-min.
‪So why is she going this far--
‪This is what I think.
‪If Kyung-ho has feelings for her,
‪she might reconsider. No?
‪I'm curious about Kyung-ho too.
‪What?
‪Wait, so everyone wants to
‪have a chat with Kyung-ho?
‪-He's three people's first choice.
‪-Man.
‪So I don't want Kyung-ho and I…
‪-You don't want to go out?
‪-No.
‪He said he is curious about other people,
‪so if we got paired up again,
‪I'd feel uncomfortable
‪and feel bad for him
‪that we got matched again.
‪What about you?
‪Do-geon is my first choice.
‪If I had to name a second choice,
‪it would be Kyung-ho.
‪Really? He's very popular.
‪I want to go out with Ha-yoon tomorrow.
‪But I'd like to chat with Kyung-ho
‪at least once.
‪Do you know what's funny?
‪We all have different first choices,
‪but because of our second choice…
‪KYUNG-HO,
‪THREE PEOPLE'S SECOND CHOICE
‪One thing went wrong,
‪and nothing went my way.
‪I couldn't get my thoughts straight.
‪So I wanted to chat to someone,
‪so I wanted to be king but I couldn't,
‪and now,
‪I probably can't go out with Ga-yeon.
‪So I figured I should have
‪a real talk with her tonight.
‪But guess what? Do-geon took her away.
‪I was very frustrated and annoyed.
‪So how did I seem today?
‪You have a very playful side.
‪I could hear Ga-yeon and Do-geon's
‪conversation from afar.
‪As soon as I heard that…
‪What is he doing? What?
‪-What the heck?
‪-What?
‪Is this a secret conversation?
‪-No.
‪May I borrow her for just five minutes?
‪-Sure.
‪-Me?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Okay.
‪-Three minutes.
‪-Take your time.
‪-That's it.
‪-Bravo!
‪Just go and stir everything up!
‪The two "everyone's second choices"
‪are chatting.
‪I'll be back.
‪-This way.
‪-Okay.
‪I was very surprised.
‪Was he so interested in her
‪that he took her away
‪while I was chatting with her?
‪I felt bad for Do-geon,
‪but I had to say something to her.
‪THE TWO GO TO A SECLUDED PLACE
‪Is there someone you want to
‪go on a date with tomorrow?
‪Tomorrow?
‪Oh my. They went somewhere
‪where there are no cameras?
‪The video quality is so bad
‪it drives the viewers crazy.
‪I don't know how much they zoomed in.
‪Is there someone you want to
‪go on a date with tomorrow?
‪Tomorrow?
‪-I mean…
‪-I…
‪First of all, as you may have noticed too,
‪it's pretty obvious, right?
‪-Yeah.
‪-You can kind of see it.
‪I can see how you feel too.
‪But
‪I don't know if this is
‪a romantic interest or not,
‪but I keep finding myself looking at you.
‪You're funny, and I'm curious about you.
‪But if I got a chance
‪to go on a date with someone,
‪I would probably go out
‪with my first choice.
‪-What about you?
‪-Me?
‪From the moment I got here,
‪I've been curious about you.
‪-Me?
‪-Yeah.
‪I came here to tell you that I want to go
‪on a date with you tomorrow.
‪You may be confused because of how things
‪are going between me and Ye-rim.
‪-I…
‪-You two seemed
‪very certain about each other.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪I thought
‪it was clear too.
‪No, it was never clear for me.
‪Honestly,
‪I was curious about both you and Ye-rim.
‪But since I was more curious about Ye-rim,
‪I went on a date with her first.
‪I was curious about you
‪from the start too.
‪I just wanted to go on a date with you.
‪He suddenly said something that was
‪almost like a confession of his feelings.
‪I couldn't help but keep looking at him,
‪but we didn't have a chance to chat.
‪So when he told me that,
‪I realized that it wasn't just me
‪who felt that way.
‪Anyway, I didn't think I'd get a chance
‪to tell you if I didn't do it today.
‪That's why I really wanted to be king.
‪-You already got to be king.
‪-I did.
‪You prevented me from going on a date.
‪Actually, that was…
‪It was on purpose?
‪I was being childish when I did that.
‪I'm serious.
‪I'm allowed to be a bit greedy, right?
‪Our eyes kept meeting, didn't they?
‪It wasn't in my head, right?
‪-You kept glaring at me.
‪-You know,
‪when I look into people's eyes,
‪-they avoid it.
‪-Yeah.
‪But you never looked away.
‪No.
‪-You'd stare at me intensely.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Why?
‪-What?
‪You were the person
‪where my eyes kept landing on.
‪To be honest,
‪you have the face
‪that is really my type.
‪-My face?
‪-Yeah.
‪Don't take that as a confession.
‪Not at all.
‪-Me too. Honestly, I'm just curious.
‪-I'm just telling you how I feel.
‪-We're curious.
‪-I'm curious so I want to go out with you.
‪I also have to give Ye-rim an answer.
‪But without tying up
‪the loose ends with you,
‪I don't want to give an answer to Ye-rim,
‪whether it's yes or no.
‪I don't know. I just want to
‪go on a date with you.
‪I thought Ga-yeon must've been
‪completely clueless about how I felt.
‪To be honest,
‪I think just that was enough.
‪The fact that he called me over to talk
‪was a huge statement in itself.
‪It's as big as Jung-min holding my hand.
‪My heart was racing.
‪Because it's not like
‪I had no interest in him at all.
‪So my heart fluttered a lot.
‪Let's chat.
‪Even if it isn't a date?
‪-A date would be nice.
‪-Yeah.
‪WHILE GA-YEON WAS CALLED AWAY,
‪DO-GEON WENT TO SEE JUNG-MIN
‪Can I ask you something?
‪How many people are you interested in?
‪All of a sudden?
‪So far, there's only one.
‪-One person you're sure about?
‪-Yeah, Ga-yeon.
‪I found Ga-yeon really compatible with me.
‪What about you?
‪It's Chae-rin for me.
‪Yeah, I think you only have one too.
‪Of course, I'm sure about Chae-rin.
‪I sense a "but."
‪But the person that I want to get to know
‪is Ga-yeon.
‪Really?
‪Hey, man.
‪You're making me nervous.
‪He should've been nervous before that.
‪You should've been nervous
‪when they went to that tent!
‪Now is not the time for a face mask!
‪-You know what? Jung-min is so innocent.
‪-Right!
‪He's a really good guy.
‪He doesn't have anyone else
‪he wants to get to know better.
‪He only has eyes for Ga-yeon.
‪Hey, man.
‪You're making me nervous.
‪For real?
‪But after today,
‪I think I'll be able to make up my mind.
‪I'll come barging in later.
‪Anytime.
‪But you may have to hurry.
‪-Why?
‪-Right now…
‪RETURNS TO THE TENT
‪-Is Do-geon lying down?
‪-Yeah, he's over there.
‪Can I take a look?
‪-I was checking the temperature.
‪-He wants to join.
‪-No.
‪-Should the three of us sleep together?
‪-No, that's not it at all.
‪-In the middle.
‪I'll sleep in the middle.
‪-Sleeping here must be really nice.
‪-Really?
‪-It isn't as bad as it seems.
‪-Right.
‪Anyway, don't freeze to death, you two.
‪See you alive.
‪-I'll get going.
‪-Good night.
‪Bye.
‪You're popular.
‪No.
‪What did you talk about?
‪He said he has been wanting to
‪have a conversation with me.
‪Are you set on someone?
‪First of all,
‪the person that I have
‪the strongest romantic interest in
‪is Jung-min.
‪KYUNG-HO CAME TO SEE JUNG-MIN
‪I have something to tell you.
‪-Really?
‪-Yes.
‪Why does everyone have something
‪to tell me? Starting with Do-geon.
‪It isn't something you'd like to hear.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪It's just how I feel.
‪I've been interested in Ga-yeon
‪from the start as well.
‪Really? Okay.
‪I've been curious about Ga-yeon.
‪I pulled her aside and told her just now
‪that I would like to
‪go on a date with her.
‪But that's just how I feel.
‪I just came here to tell you
‪that I told her that.
‪Thanks for letting me know.
‪I feel like I can't just sit back
‪and do nothing now.
‪Right. Honestly…
‪This is hilarious.
‪I didn't want to be underhanded about it.
‪This is interesting.
‪Another one came. It was Kyung-ho.
‪I realized right then
‪that I shouldn't just sit back.
‪I should do something.
‪I need to have a chat with Ga-yeon.
‪THE PHANTOM OF GANGHWADO RUSHES OUT
‪He's going out too?
‪Ga-yeon's getting summoned again?
‪What about Do-geon?
‪I just couldn't get
‪paired up with Jung-min, so…
‪My closest friend is…
‪-Ga-yeon!
‪-Yeah?
‪-You have a face mask on?
‪-Who's that? Are you on the left?
‪Okay, there you are.
‪Aren't you cold?
‪-I'm fine with this on.
‪-Really?
‪I was about to go to bed,
‪but I came out to have a chat with you.
‪What is that?
‪You want me to chat with you
‪looking like that?
‪-Shall we talk?
‪-Okay.
‪I'll be back.
‪-Go on inside.
‪-Okay, I'll be inside.
‪Man, this face mask.
‪Take it off.
‪-I don't think we can chat with that on.
‪-Right.
‪-Gosh, Ga-yeon.
‪-Yeah?
‪-All the guys have come to see me.
‪-Why?
‪They like you.
‪-Why are they being like this suddenly?
‪-I know.
‪-What are they talking about?
‪I want to know how you feel.
‪I honestly don't care about the guys.
‪If I'm going to be
‪completely honest with you,
‪you are the only person
‪I'm romantically interested in.
‪The one I have
‪clear feelings for, that is.
‪How many times do I have to hear
‪that Jung-min is her first choice?
‪She said like ten times
‪that she doesn't know if it's romantic
‪but she keeps looking at Kyung-ho!
‪Make it stop!
‪The problem is the "but."
‪-But…
‪-But?
‪-Yeah, but?
‪-But…
‪-I find myself
‪-Yes.
‪-keep looking at Kyung-ho.
‪-I see.
‪And I think the way
‪he jokes around is funny.
‪But I really don't know
‪if this is romantic interest or not.
‪But I know for sure is that
‪you are my first choice at the moment.
‪Then, who do you think is the right person
‪for you to go on a date with tomorrow?
‪I already told this to Hye-won.
‪-Tomorrow?
‪-I said I want to go out with you.
‪As for me,
‪there's no second choice at the moment.
‪-So far.
‪-There's only me?
‪-For me, yes.
‪-You can talk
‪-to someone.
‪-There's no second choice.
‪You're the only one for me right now.
‪I came to see you immediately
‪because I didn't want to lose you.
‪He said there's no second choice.
‪He reassured me
‪by being straightforward to me.
‪What Jung-min said made
‪my heart flutter a bit more.
‪Hang out with me tomorrow.
‪I want to.
‪And I think it'll turn out that way.
‪I think Hye-won is willing
‪to make things happen for me.
‪You're right.
‪From what I can get,
‪Kyung-ho hasn't voted for me.
‪He voted for her.
‪He voted for me yesterday and today.
‪But along with those hearts,
‪he gave me a bunch of negative hearts.
‪That means he doesn't want me
‪to be king no matter what.
‪And I know why he did that.
‪It's because I told him
‪I would choose him if it were up to me.
‪He didn't want that to happen,
‪and that's probably why--
‪You don't know for sure that
‪Kyung-ho gave you the negative hearts.
‪I couldn't think of anyone besides him
‪who would give me those.
‪He gave me a bunch of negative hearts
‪so I couldn't pick him.
‪-No.
‪-Really? Why? It makes total sense to me.
‪-No, that's not it.
‪Why not?
‪-Come on.
‪-Look.
‪I'm sorry, but ladies.
‪-Don't make her a fool. Just tell her.
‪-Exactly!
‪-I would tell her.
‪-Tell her.
‪It's okay. I would tell her.
‪I felt so guilty. I gave her ten of those.
‪What if she and Kyung-ho fall out
‪because of what I did? I was worried.
‪I have to fix it. What do I do?
‪I was panicking.
‪I think you're Kyung-ho's first choice.
‪-Yeah.
‪-But
‪that's a separate matter.
‪-You think he gave you the black hearts?
‪-Yeah.
‪-No.
‪But today, I was…
‪-He really didn't.
‪-For real?
‪-For real.
‪-Why do you think that?
‪-The black hearts…
‪I didn't use any of the black hearts.
‪Is that possible? I don't know.
‪-But I definitely don't think he did…
‪-Why?
‪Why do you think that?
‪-I don't think he'd do that.
‪-Yeah.
‪How many black hearts did you get?
‪It was so many I gave up counting.
‪-What?
‪-Really?
‪Was it a few dozen?
‪It was over 15.
‪-Over 15?
‪-I stopped counting after 15.
‪Why were there so many?
‪She said she got over ten.
‪I was relieved, but at the same time,
‪I wondered who gave her those.
‪The emptier the jar gets,
‪the easier it is to tell
‪how many hearts that person used.
‪I didn't see that.
‪-I didn't see that.
‪-I saw it while grabbing mine.
‪But it was clear that he used up a lot.
‪I think he exchanged all those hearts
‪with black hearts and gave them to me.
‪That would be a real shock.
‪-I wanted to be king,
‪-Yeah?
‪so I exchanged about 70 Heart Chips
‪for the black ones
‪and gave everyone
‪ten black chips except for me.
‪That's why I had black chips.
‪I wondered who they were from.
‪I was trying to increase
‪my chances of becoming the king.
‪I went that far today,
‪but it still didn't work out,
‪so I got a headache.
‪But now that I've talked to her,
‪my head feels a lot lighter now.
‪I hope you aren't too deflated
‪over Kyung-ho,
‪because to me it seems like he makes
‪his feelings for you very clear.
‪Well, he does,
‪but it feels like he's leaving me hanging
‪when he wants to get to know someone else.
‪-Like, keeping me as an option.
‪-That's how you feel?
‪That's how I feel about
‪why he gave me those hearts.
‪And when he calls my name
‪after having fun with Ga-yeon,
‪it feels like he's being
‪a dog in the manger.
‪-No.
‪-That was infuriating.
‪Your feelings for him are so strong
‪-that you may be reading into things.
‪-Right.
‪You're still a baby.
‪Don't read into things.
‪The important thing is
‪that you are his first choice.
‪But it would hurt me more
‪if that turned out to be false.
‪I don't think I would act like him
‪unless I'm sure of the other person.
‪But I might be feeling this way because
‪I have such strong feelings for him.
‪It might not be a big deal,
‪but I might just be overthinking it.
‪What if Ga-yeon and Kyung-ho go on a date?
‪If they go on a date?
‪Be happy, you two.
‪"Be happy, you two."
‪Do you think you'll lose feelings for him?
‪Since I know how he was with me,
‪I can expect how he'll be
‪with someone else too.
‪I don't think I'd like that.
‪You know, given how she acts, I thought
‪Ga-yeon's first choice might be Kyung-ho.
‪I think
‪-there's only a tiny difference.
‪-I agree.
‪We got to talk about things like this
‪and share how we really felt.
‪Yeah.
‪Oh my. Sorry.
‪Are you done now?
‪-Yeah, we're done.
‪-Really?
‪-Good night.
‪-Yeah.
‪-You two are too close.
‪It's warmer than I thought.
‪What was your first impression of me?
‪-You stood out the most.
‪-Really?
‪-You have well-defined features.
‪-My features?
‪So I thought, "Wow."
‪I was so awkward and shy yesterday.
‪-Yeah?
‪-I felt kind of…
‪I think you talked
‪a lot yesterday, though.
‪Really? So am I too talkative today?
‪That's why I became
‪more interested in you.
‪I like someone who talks a lot.
‪-Wow, I'm getting too comfortable here.
‪-Right?
‪-What time is it?
‪-It's 4:11 a.m.
‪No way.
‪You kept getting called away.
‪-No, I wasn't.
‪-Yes, you were.
‪You got called away and didn't come back.
‪I just wandered about here.
‪What should we do?
‪-Let's wash up.
‪-Shall we?
‪-It's too late.
‪-Let's get some sleep.
‪-What?
‪-You're really tall.
‪You're tall.
‪Are you here to do something?
‪-We came to wash up.
‪-You came to wash up?
‪-Wash up then.
‪-Why are you still up?
‪Well, I had a chat.
‪-With whom?
‪-I couldn't sleep.
‪-What?
‪With Hye-won.
‪Oh, Hye-won.
‪A serious conversation.
‪-A serious conversation?
‪-She's the king.
‪Yeah, be on her good side.
‪Do you think I'm on her good side?
‪Well, you were a tyrant yesterday.
‪What?
‪What are you talking about?
‪You were a tyrant.
‪In what way?
‪Because I didn't let you guys go out?
‪No, I'm just kidding.
‪I know.
‪-You know?
‪-Yeah.
‪Why do you keep switching between
‪speaking casually and speaking formally?
‪Sorry.
‪I won't do it.
‪Are you going to wash up?
‪-Can I go to bed like this?
‪-I don't think so.
‪-I don't know.
‪-What should I wear to bed?
‪Want to borrow my zip-up hoodie?
‪I'd love that.
‪Put this on.
‪Thank you.
‪It's nice and thick.
‪That's perfect. Thanks.
‪-Wash up.
‪-Good night.
‪Knock, knock.
‪-Did you wash up?
‪-Yeah.
‪Here's some red ginseng
‪and de-puffing candy.
‪For real? Thank you.
‪Since you're sleeping outside,
‪take that before you go to bed.
‪And take this in the morning.
‪You can take that one now
‪or take them together.
‪When I spoke with Do-geon,
‪he said Chae-rin is his first choice,
‪so you don't have to worry.
‪I don't think Chae-rin was worried at all.
‪Yeah, I could tell.
‪These two are steady.
‪How do you feel, Ye-rim?
‪I would like you and Kyung-ho
‪to have a conversation.
‪-Me?
‪-Yeah.
‪Is there anyone else
‪you'd like to get to know, Ye-rim?
‪There's no one
‪I really want to get to know,
‪but I'm not determined to make things work
‪with my first choice either.
‪Me too.
‪Because of his job and age,
‪I was really conflicted,
‪-to be honest.
‪-You were?
‪Why?
‪He only has qualities I'm not really into.
‪-Really?
‪-He's younger and he is in the arts.
‪-Acting, at that.
‪-Gosh.
‪I thought it wouldn't matter,
‪but I was a bit…
‪Really?
‪I was a bit disappointed.
‪If he is a good person despite all that,
‪I'd go ahead with it,
‪but I would have to find that out
‪for the rest of my time here.
‪You should try
‪and talk with others too,
‪if you get a chance.
‪Yeah.
‪His job and age
‪weren't what I expected,
‪but that doesn't mean
‪I want to close that door.
‪I decided to be
‪more level-headed about him.
‪If I like him despite his job and age,
‪that'd mean he's a really good person.
‪Are you cleaning up by yourself?
‪Yeah, I just wanted to tidy up.
‪Isn't it cold out there?
‪It's warmer than I thought.
‪If I had known it'd be warm,
‪I would have picked you.
‪Why didn't you pick me?
‪I thought no one wanted to go.
‪Hey, you're pretty good at that.
‪No joke, right?
‪Yeah, no joke.
‪What time do you want to get dolled up?
‪I'm going to open up tomorrow.
‪What time should I come?
‪About 10 a.m.?
‪Okay, got it.
‪Sleep well.
‪-Good night.
‪What do you think will happen from now on?
‪What are you going to do?
‪I'll just follow my heart.
‪I think everybody is going to
‪want to come here now.
‪-Here?
‪-Yeah.
‪-With someone they like?
‪What's going on? I sense some spark here.
‪-Here?
‪-Yeah.
‪-With someone they like?
‪Then it would be amazing
‪to come here on the last night.
‪I know. It seems like a punishment but…
‪-Yeah, but it's also an opportunity.
‪-Yeah.
‪It can be an opportunity.
‪It can be a chance
‪for the relationship to deepen.
‪Would you like to come back again
‪with Chae-rin?
‪Yeah, if I can…
‪I don't want to come back here.
‪Good night.
‪GA-YEON WAKES UP
‪7:40 A.M.
‪Do-geon, are you asleep?
‪Are you?
‪It's 7:40 a.m.
‪Shall we go inside?
‪-Bye.
‪THEY ARE GOING TO GET SOME MORE SLEEP
‪How was it? Did you sleep well?
‪Do-geon and I were so tired,
‪so we went straight to sleep.
‪I couldn't fall asleep, but he did.
‪No way.
‪There was nothing romantic about it.
‪Then,
‪you don't recommend it?
‪It would be nice
‪if you and Do-geon went there.
‪If you go with someone you like,
‪you'd want to hold hands.
‪-For real?
‪-Yeah.
‪I think
‪it'll be a huge advantage
‪if you go on the third or fourth night.
‪-What kind of place is it?
‪-I don't know.
‪-Aren't you cold?
‪-What?
‪-No.
‪Are you wearing that today?
‪Yeah, I wore what seemed most comfortable.
‪I'm sorry you didn't get any sleep.
‪The tent was shocking.
‪-Is Do-geon sleeping? Where is he?
‪-What?
‪He isn't in our room.
‪What?
‪-Isn't he sleeping out there?
‪-Really?
‪2ND ROUND OF DEEP SLEEP
‪Close your eyes.
‪Let me contour your jawline.
‪I wonder what kind of date we'll go on.
‪-What?
‪-I wonder what kind of date we'll go on.
‪-Done.
‪-Thank you.
‪AFTER HIS DEEP SLEEP,
‪DO-GEON FINISHED GETTING READY FIRST
‪Do-geon.
‪I heard you slept well by yourself.
‪-You snored.
‪-Really?
‪She kept chattering away next to me.
‪She wouldn't stop chattering beside me.
‪Did we go to bed at 4 a.m.?
‪We fell asleep after 5 a.m.
‪-What did you talk about?
‪-It's a secret.
‪-Don't ask.
‪-He was so nervous he couldn't sleep.
‪I think he slept well.
‪I almost couldn't wake up.
‪But you see,
‪I think that tent can be something.
‪Like a turning point?
‪If you're sure about someone…
‪Sounds fun. Let's do it.
‪Let's do it.
‪-Just enjoy it.
‪-Let's do all of it.
‪I am
‪not going to use my brain starting today.
‪Want some?
‪What do you want to do?
‪I just want to see the ocean again.
‪The ocean again?
‪I want to see the ocean,
‪but there wasn't any water there.
‪-It's a mudflat.
‪-Yeah.
‪You have to time it right.
‪Stop acting like a know-it-all.
‪I told you that.
‪After getting some sleep,
‪I felt much better.
‪She felt better after getting some sleep.
‪These people are driven by instinct.
‪-How cute.
‪-She's so simple.
‪Last night, Chae-rin told me
‪that Jung-min devised a scheme
‪regarding the Heart Chips.
‪I suspect that Kyung-ho
‪gave me the black hearts.
‪-Why though?
‪-Because
‪he wanted to chat with his second choice.
‪I don't think so.
‪I hope it isn't the case too.
‪-I don't think so.
‪-Yay.
‪The Black Heart Chips in my box…
‪I just gave them to you.
‪-Is that why I had so many?
‪-Yeah.
‪What the heck?
‪After I found out
‪that Chae-rin put some in
‪and Jung-min's alliance put some in,
‪I wondered, "Did Kyung-ho not put any in?"
‪And it made me feel much better.
‪Until yesterday, I felt uncomfortable
‪around him and I wanted to avoid him,
‪but I was happy to see him in the morning.
‪We talked quite a bit after that
‪and I thought, "I won't feel
‪so awkward if this keeps up."
‪Was deciding people's dates
‪the king's privilege yesterday?
‪Not everyone.
‪Only a few.
‪Oh, only a few?
‪Isn't that right?
‪-She decides for everyone.
‪-It's for everyone.
‪You want a few left behind again?
‪I thought we were talking about
‪yesterday's king.
‪You aren't king anymore.
‪You've been dethroned.
‪All right, guys.
‪I was talking about yesterday's king.
‪But the new king is a bit…
‪I think the new king is the real tyrant.
‪No, I'm not.
‪-You see?
‪-He was a good king.
‪-He was.
‪-No, I think she is a good king.
‪-Right?
‪Do you guys want me to go nuts?
‪I might ruin everything.
‪I mean…
‪Everybody is…
‪Go get it.
‪A LETTER HAS ARRIVED IN THE MAILBOX
‪I've never done this before.
‪"From now on, you will get
‪an audience with the king,
‪where you can make your case
‪to match you with the person you want."
‪THE KING'S OFFICE IS OPEN AGAIN TODAY
‪The second king, Jung Hye-won,
‪may decide the dates for everyone today
‪and can personally decide
‪all the date activities as well.
‪1. DIG SHELLFISH AT THE MUDFLAT AND EAT
‪KOREAN CHINESE FOOD (30,000 WON DATE)
‪2. CAFE AND GRILLED SHELLFISH
‪3. FOOT BATH AND BARBECUE
‪4. CRAFT STUDIO AND ITALIAN RESTAURANT
‪Those granted an audience
‪may make their case for five minutes.
‪-Hello.
‪You look classy today as well.
‪Thank you.
‪THE FIRST PETITIONER IS DO-GEON
‪Make your case
‪for five minutes starting now.
‪-Anything you want.
‪-Five minutes?
‪If you say what you want to say
‪and who you want,
‪I'll take good care of it.
‪Ready, go.
‪-I really respect you, Your Majesty.
‪-Right?
‪-You don't seem like a tyrant at all.
‪-I don't, right?
‪I'll try to become
‪an even more amazing king.
‪You're already plenty amazing.
‪I just thought that
‪I should flatter the king
‪as much as I could.
‪Understood.
‪I'll remember that.
‪First of all,
‪I'd like to go on a date
‪with Ye-rim today.
‪PREFERRED DATE
‪DO-GEON CHOOSES YE-RIM
‪It isn't Chae-rin?
‪I'd like to go on a date with Ye-rim.
‪PREFERRED DATE
‪DO-GEON CHOOSES YE-RIM
‪The king is surprised.
‪Of course, I'd like to go with Chae-rin,
‪but she may have
‪someone else she wants to talk to.
‪Where would you like to go?
‪Can I decide the activity too?
‪You can make your case.
‪Tell me where you want to go.
‪THERE ARE FOUR OPTIONS
‪"Dig for shellfish at the mudflat?" Jeez.
‪I pick
‪the cafe and grilled shellfish.
‪Cafe?
‪-Cafe and shellfish.
‪-Got it.
‪Got it. I'll remember that.
‪-You'll remember, right?
‪-I will.
‪Don't send me to the mudflat.
‪I'll remember what you said.
‪Please.
‪Bye.
‪Your Majesty.
‪You're here.
‪-It must be so hard for you.
‪-It is a weighty responsibility.
‪Should I have brought a snack?
‪It was like a noble lady
‪was sitting there.
‪"Milady."
‪"What are you doing in this shabby place?"
‪It was like sitting across
‪from a tarot reader.
‪All right. Tell me what you want to say
‪for five minutes, Chae-rin.
‪I would
‪like to go out with
‪either Do-geon or Kyung-ho.
‪Do-geon or Kyung-ho?
‪PREFERRED DATES
‪DO-GEON, KYUNG-HO
‪-What's this?
‪-Pick where you'd like to go.
‪I'm kind of feeling
‪the digging for shellfish one.
‪Digging for shellfish at the mudflat?
‪Definitely this one.
‪Really?
‪I wanted to do the mudflat one
‪as soon as I saw it.
‪It would be a very unique date.
‪I just picked what I wanted to do.
‪I didn't think about
‪who else might choose it.
‪Welcome.
‪Yes, Your Majesty.
‪I'd like to go out with Ga-yeon.
‪Ga-yeon?
‪I have the strongest feelings
‪for Ga-yeon,
‪and I think the feelings are mutual.
‪If I don't get to
‪go on a date with her today,
‪it'd be a shame for both of us.
‪So I would definitely like to
‪go on a date with her today.
‪I gave Hye-won a lot of Heart Chips
‪as a part of our plot.
‪I was convinced
‪that Hye-won would definitely pair us up.
‪Where do you want to go?
‪Ga-yeon seemed very tired.
‪I choose the foot bath and barbecue.
‪So that she can relax.
‪The mudflat is my second choice.
‪-The mudflat?
‪-Yes.
‪Something active might actually
‪be better when you're tired.
‪Jung-min thinks a lot about Ga-yeon.
‪-He's considerate.
‪-He's a good guy.
‪Got it. Thank you.
‪-Thank you.
‪-All right.
‪-Welcome.
‪-Hello.
‪I would…
‪I would like to go on a date with Ga-yeon.
‪I want to go on a date with Ga-yeon.
‪My reason for that is
‪because I want to be sure
‪about the situation I am in
‪since it's such a short period.
‪I used to be more sure about how I felt.
‪It was clear.
‪But after our date,
‪I started having
‪some second thoughts about Ye-rim,
‪so I didn't have a clear first choice.
‪Some might say
‪that things are going pretty well for me.
‪But actually,
‪I've been struggling a lot internally,
‪to be honest.
‪My head was hurting so much that
‪I couldn't organize my thoughts or focus.
‪The case I want to make with you is
‪that I'd like you to give me
‪time to organize my thoughts
‪and to get to know the other person.
‪I hope you can grant me that.
‪Very well noted.
‪Then, is there somewhere
‪you would like to go, Kyung-ho?
‪I pick the foot bath or craft studio.
‪Foot bath or craft studio?
‪As for the foot bath,
‪I use my feet a lot in my job.
‪But that aside,
‪-it is--
‪-You made a good case.
‪-This is perfect.
‪-Right?
‪KYUNG-HO'S FAN
‪Treatment.
‪I haven't been able to do it lately.
‪I have to practice, but…
‪That breaks my heart.
‪-Treatment.
‪-Yes.
‪Understood. I'll take note.
‪-Thank you.
‪THE TREATMENT GUY
‪WHO TARGETED HIS FAN'S HEART LEAVES
‪-Hello.
‪-Hello, Ye-rim.
‪Oh, gosh.
‪FIFTH PETITIONER, YE-RIM
‪Last night, I begged you not to
‪pair me up with Kyung-ho, right?
‪But today,
‪I feel differently.
‪It would be nice to go out with Kyung-ho.
‪PREFERRED DATE
‪YE-RIM CHOOSES KYUNG-HO
‪Great. What a relief.
‪But…
‪I'm curious about Do-geon too.
‪-Do-geon?
‪-Yes.
‪-Where do you want to go?
‪-Where do I want to go?
‪The craft studio
‪or digging for shellfish at the mudflat?
‪Really? I think you'd look so cute.
‪Dig some up
‪so we can make ‪kalguksu‪ with it.
‪That sounds amazing.
‪-It'll work out for you.
‪-Will it work out for me?
‪Okay. See you.
‪Welcome, my love.
‪It suits you, Hye-won.
‪Does it suit me? Thank you.
‪First of all,
‪the person who I definitely have
‪romantic feelings for is Jung-min.
‪But I had
‪-a chat with Kyung-ho yesterday.
‪-Okay.
‪He really
‪opened up to me about how he felt.
‪So I told him honestly
‪that I'm not sure what I feel for him
‪is romantic or not.
‪What is a romantic feeling?
‪Tell me the exact definition of it,
‪Ga-yeon.
‪I don't know how many times
‪I've heard "romantic feelings" today.
‪-Ga-yeon, please tell me.
‪-Look.
‪-Hey.
‪-You're driving me crazy.
‪-It's too soon to get angry.
‪-For real?
‪She hasn't even mentioned
‪how she keeps looking at him yet.
‪She hasn't brought up
‪how she gazes at him yet.
‪…is romantic or not.
‪But I keep finding myself gazing at him.
‪I understand.
‪I leave my fate in your hands.
‪All right.
‪PREFERRED DATE
‪GA-YEON CHOOSES KYUNG-HO
‪-Thank you.
‪Hello.
‪-Hello, Your Majesty.
‪-Hello.
‪As I said yesterday,
‪I'd like to go on a date with you.
‪Since yesterday,
‪I've been feeling sure about it.
‪So that's what I want.
‪PREFERRED DATE
‪HA-YOON CHOOSES HYE-WON
‪Good.
‪What?
‪"Good."
‪Let's hear it one more time.
‪Let's hear "Good" one more time.
‪Good.
‪The breathy voice. They'd love it at JYP.
‪-My ears are being tickled.
‪-It's tingling.
‪-Can we hear it one more time?
‪-Jeez.
‪Good.
‪-Where do you want to go?
‪-I want to go with you.
‪With the most genuine gaze,
‪Ha-yoon calmly and sincerely said,
‪"I want to go on a date with you."
‪He came across as so reliable
‪and not pushy at all.
‪I was really touched.
‪Do you like risotto and stuff like that?
‪-The king does not like things like that.
‪-Then,
‪what about foot bath and barbecue?
‪Foot bath and barbecue?
‪-One of these two.
‪-First and second choice?
‪The king will take it into consideration
‪and she will consider
‪whether she wants to go with you too.
‪-Of course.
‪-Then, I'll let you know.
‪-Yes.
‪-Okay.
‪-I trust you'll make a wise decision.
‪-Of course.
‪-All right.
‪-I'll remember that. Goodbye.
‪-Bye.
‪THE LAST PETITIONER LEAVES
‪I think I made the right choice.
‪INSTRUCTIONS FOR KING OF HEARTS
‪THE POWER TO DECIDE THE DATES
‪THE KING FINISHED MAKING ALL THE DECISIONS
‪You see, it seems like--
‪-Your Majesty!
‪-It was so difficult.
‪-Well done.
‪-Come and sit.
‪It was really…
‪That's the weight of being the king.
‪-Okay.
‪-There was nothing I could do.
‪-I'm sorry.
‪-Sorry about what?
‪-I can't look at anybody.
‪-It's okay.
‪I wonder what the decisions are.
‪-I'm nervous.
‪-Go get it.
‪POLITE BOW
‪So he knew how to be polite?
‪You can tell he was a royal.
‪Read it for us.
‪"As per the decision
‪of the second king, Jung Hye-won…"
‪Pay attention.
‪"…you have been paired up as follows."
‪I'll mix them and give them out randomly,
‪so please read them out loud.
‪THE DATE PAIRING CARDS ARE GIVEN RANDOMLY
‪Foot bath and barbecue.
‪Who's going?
‪Ye-rim
‪and Do-geon.
‪In the morning,
‪I playfully asked Do-geon
‪what it'd be like if we went on a date.
‪And he requested for me.
‪So I was a bit surprised.
‪He actually requested
‪to go on a date with me?
‪Oh my. I'm getting butterflies.
‪We've only seen Do-geon
‪-as the younger guy.
‪-Yeah.
‪We'll see what he's like
‪-to a younger woman.
‪-Exactly.
‪I told you today, didn't I?
‪-Yeah. Nice.
‪-I said we'd go out.
‪I really didn't want
‪Do-geon and Ye-rim to be paired.
‪I secretly hoped that
‪Do-geon and Ye-rim wouldn't be paired.
‪After this date,
‪our first choices might change.
‪"Cafe and grilled shellfish."
‪How romantic.
‪"Ga-yeon…
‪and Kyung-ho."
‪Yeah.
‪And Jung-min ended up announcing that.
‪-What is this?
‪-How could you?
‪I'm so sorry.
‪What a cruel king.
‪You need some time apart.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Right?
‪She basically betrayed me.
‪We're the ones who made Hye-won king.
‪I guess, Ga-yeon's second choice
‪was Kyung-ho.
‪But the kind king
‪didn't know Ga-yeon's second choice,
‪so I think she just paired them.
‪They were paired at uncanny timing,
‪so I got a bit nervous.
‪Honestly, I was happy.
‪I had this heaviness right here.
‪I felt like a weight
‪had been lifted off my chest.
‪I thought, "Hey, what's going on?"
‪Until last night, Ga-yeon named Jung-min
‪as her definite first choice,
‪so I thought she'd go out with Jung-min.
‪I knew I'd be going out with Kyung-ho.
‪-What?
‪-What? She knew?
‪-Let's see.
‪-I'm scared.
‪-Let's see what happened.
‪-I'm scared, Joo-heon!
‪LAST NIGHT
‪Come over here.
‪-Who do you want to go out with?
‪-What?
‪The date?
‪Gosh.
‪What about you?
‪Me?
‪The person I find fun
‪and my eyes are drawn to is Kyung-ho.
‪You want to check for yourself, right?
‪Originally, we had agreed that
‪Jung-min and I would go out
‪and Ha-yoon and Hye-won would go out.
‪We had a secret chat of sorts.
‪If I go out with Jung-min tomorrow…
‪I don't know.
‪I know.
‪I'm going to follow your decision.
‪I'm glad I became king.
‪You shook everything up.
‪I gave her my opinion.
‪"Instead of this combination,
‪these two might be good too."
‪"I hope it can go this way."
‪And Hye-won was in agreement with me.
‪Those two seem so good together,
‪in my opinion.
‪I had to see them together.
‪And Ga-yeon played a role
‪in my decision too.
‪I think Ga-yeon wanted to
‪go on a date with Kyung-ho more.
‪I think that Kyung-ho and I
‪look good together, appearance-wise.
‪That's why I thought of us
‪getting paired up.
‪Do-geon and Ye-rim are
‪around the same age, right?
‪We decided to shake everything up.
‪I knew it wasn't the deal
‪our alliance agreed on,
‪but I wanted to pair Ga-yeon and Kyung-ho.
‪She did as I expected.
‪So I wasn't really troubled.
‪It may seem like Hye-won is the tyrant,
‪-but there was a mastermind behind her.
‪-Right.
‪You're right.
‪There was a queen dowager
‪behind the queen.
‪That's an accurate analogy.
‪"Dig for shellfish at the mudflat and eat
‪Korean Chinese food. A 30,000 won date."
‪"Jung-min and Chae-rin."
‪Wait. What?
‪-What?
‪-Why?
‪-This is so surprising.
‪This is going to be fun.
‪How did she come up with this pairing?
‪Did she pair
‪the two funny people together?
‪In 30,000 won, both the mudflat activity
‪and Korean Chinese food are included.
‪-Goodness.
‪-What about the cost of the activity?
‪What about the work pants,
‪-boots, and small garden hoe rentals?
‪-You figure it out.
‪We should take some salt.
‪We have to take that.
‪I bet the shellfish are scared right now.
‪I'll give the shellfish a call.
‪Have fun.
‪They said they're the comedic duo
‪and everyone was laughing and all,
‪but I was secretly feeling a bit nervous.
‪As for the craft studio
‪and Italian restaurant,
‪-Hye-won and Ha-yoon will be going.
‪-Yes.
‪-The craft studio.
‪-Because I'm king.
‪-What will you make?
‪-Sounds fun.
‪Get some rest at the cafe.
‪"Get some rest"?
‪I'll bring some shellfish.
‪I think things turned out
‪the way we talked last night.
‪It went exactly that way.
‪It would be nice to
‪have a chat with everyone.
‪Yeah, to make it really different.
‪And you can be attracted
‪to a different person too.
‪-Who knows?
‪-You never know.
‪I'm excited.
‪CHAE-RIN GETS READY
‪TO GO TO THE MUDFLAT
‪You look cute.
‪Really?
‪I'll go and dig up so many.
‪Is that your battle gear?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Wow.
‪-Want to go?
‪-Are you ready, Chae?
‪I'm ready!
‪-Call me Jung.
‪-Sorry.
‪So cute.
‪Let's get going. Dinner is in our hands.
‪We have to feed our children.
‪-You're a mama bird.
‪-Yeah.
‪I feel very responsible.
‪I'm glad.
‪I didn't want to do anything too active.
‪What did you want to do?
‪-Cafe?
‪-Yeah.
‪I'm excited.
‪This is my first date.
‪Right.
‪Will it be your last date?
‪No.
‪Are you tired?
‪Yes.
‪Come and sleep here. Lie down here.
‪-The sofa?
‪-Come here.
‪-No, thanks.
‪-Why?
‪I'm going to sleep
‪while doing the foot bath.
‪I'll be talking by myself.
‪"Hello, this is Park Do-geon's vlog."
‪I could picture them together.
‪-Those two?
‪-Yeah.
‪Me too.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪They had a lot of small talk.
‪Oh, yeah?
‪-I think we look good together too.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Did you say yes?
‪Really?
‪-To be honest--
‪-But you have
‪-feelings for her.
‪-Who?
‪Ye-rim.
‪-I do.
‪-Yeah.
‪Nothing about
‪what you said to me yesterday changed?
‪-What I said to you?
‪-Yeah.
‪No change.
‪Why?
‪Worried I changed my mind overnight?
‪-While I was talking in my sleep?
‪-It can happen. Yeah.
‪But I don't think so.
‪No, it hasn't changed.
‪Have fun, Chae-rin.
‪I feel kind of awkward with Do-geon.
‪What should I talk about?
‪You feel awkward?
‪You seemed fine yesterday.
‪I was trying really hard.
‪I already told him about my school
‪and we talked about
‪our past relationships.
‪Even your past relationships? Tell me.
‪Two years and six months.
‪Started dating before the military
‪and broke up during his service.
‪-Really? For two and a half years?
‪-Yeah.
‪-I like that.
‪Anything you want to know?
‪Ask if he's interested in someone else.
‪-Are there two? Things like that.
‪-Okay.
‪Apparently, Do-geon requested for me.
‪What do you mean?
‪When he went to Hye-won…
‪-But our first choices…
‪-And he named you?
‪-Do-geon did?
‪-That's what I heard.
‪Hang on. What's going on?
‪I could tell that his second choice
‪would be Ye-rim.
‪But Ye-rim and I are close.
‪Should I choose love or friendship?
‪Well, I would actually choose love.
‪Sorry, Ye-rim.
‪This is what I'm curious about too.
‪Did he only request you?
‪And what was his thought process
‪when he asked for you?
‪-I'm curious about that too.
‪-Okay.
‪YE-RIM HAS A MISSION
‪Good.
‪What did you talk about
‪with Ga-yeon last night?
‪Ga-yeon got summoned.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪Oh, Jung-min came to see her?
‪-Is that right?
‪-What?
‪Was it Jung-min?
‪Yeah, Jung-min came and…
‪Kyung-ho came too?
‪-And so on.
‪-Really?
‪-I was like a lost puppy.
‪-I know.
‪You must've been bored.
‪-I wandered around by myself.
‪-That's funny.
‪I didn't get a chance
‪to chat with the guys much,
‪so we talked about what we'd like to do.
‪I see.
‪YE-RIM AND DO-GEON
‪ARE OFF TO THEIR DATE
‪Thank you.
‪These two look good together.
‪And he seems mature here.
‪Do-geon as the older guy.
‪How much sleep did you get?
‪I went to bed past 5 a.m.
‪How was your date yesterday?
‪-For me, it was to confirm my feelings.
‪-Right.
‪And for Kyung-ho,
‪he was still figuring things out.
‪It felt like that was his mindset.
‪I don't think it went exactly smoothly.
‪How was it for you?
‪-Yesterday?
‪-Yeah.
‪I went to confirm my feelings too.
‪And I think we get along well.
‪I had fun.
‪Then, is Chae-rin your only choice?
‪No.
‪I'm interested in Chae-rin and Ga-yeon.
‪We didn't get a chance to talk much.
‪-With Ga-yeon?
‪-Yeah.
‪Then I had to choose
‪a partner for that thing last night,
‪so I just
‪went and chose Ga-yeon.
‪Are you still curious about Ga-yeon then?
‪No, not anymore.
‪It felt like you and Chae-rin
‪-were practically a done deal, right?
‪-Yeah.
‪That's why I'm trying to keep my distance.
‪If I didn't, it'd be uncomfortable for her
‪to get to know the others.
‪And it might be difficult for the others
‪to get to know her
‪-even if they wanted to.
‪-Right.
‪Of course, if they're
‪really interested in her,
‪they might do what the other intruders
‪did to me and Ga-yeon last night.
‪That's so annoying.
‪They could do that, but…
‪That's annoying? Why?
‪Kyung-ho was one of the intruders.
‪I didn't say that.
‪Didn't you say Kyung-ho came by?
‪What?
‪-It was only Jung-min?
‪-I only mentioned Jung-min.
‪As for the rest…
‪What did I say? "A few guys"?
‪You said, "And so on."
‪-Did I?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Yeah, that means--
‪-Kyung-ho wasn't one of them?
‪That could mean that Kyung-ho was there…
‪See? You said he was there.
‪Ha-yoon could have been there too.
‪-There could've been a few guys--
‪-So was Kyung-ho one of them?
‪-I don't know.
‪-Really?
‪I'm so tired
‪that I don't remember their faces.
‪YERIM & DO-GEON
‪CAFE TRAMONTO
‪This must be it.
‪-Hello.
‪-Do we have to roll up our pants?
‪-Yeah.
‪Why don't you pour all of it in?
‪It looks like spilled orange juice.
‪Do you want a bite?
‪-It's tasty.
‪-A biscuit? Just a bite.
‪Finish it.
‪Isn't it good?
‪They look good.
‪They look like they'd date
‪for a long time.
‪Are you good at grilling meat?
‪I'm really bad at it.
‪Then, I'll do the grilling.
‪Do you not eat food that tastes bad?
‪-I can act like I'm enjoying it.
‪-Really?
‪I really like
‪someone who would act like
‪an ice cream sandwich is hot
‪-if I asked them to do it.
‪-Oh.
‪Like this?
‪Seriously.
‪Someone who goes above and beyond
‪without worrying about other people.
‪Someone who plays along with her.
‪That isn't Kyung-ho.
‪Kyung-ho would say,
‪"Why do I have to do something like that?"
‪You like someone funny too.
‪Well, I'd like to be
‪a fun person to be around.
‪-Do you think I'm fun to be around?
‪-You?
‪You are good at talking.
‪What is this…
‪You sound like a kindergarten teacher
‪phoning a parent.
‪"Ye-rim was
‪so quiet that we had no idea,
‪but she finally started talking."
‪That's hilarious.
‪Seriously.
‪She likes men like that.
‪Ye-rim is smiling a lot.
‪Yeah.
‪We seemed to be on the same wavelength.
‪Which led me to think,
‪"What if I'd chosen
‪Do-geon from the start?"
‪I wonder what it would have been like
‪if I had been the one sitting next to him,
‪having casual conversations.
‪I don't think he would
‪make things difficult for anyone.
‪Then I wouldn't have had to show
‪my raw emotions to the others.
‪You must have voted
‪for only one person yesterday.
‪I voted for you too.
‪-Me?
‪-Yeah.
‪Did I put it in the wrong box?
‪-Yesterday?
‪-Yeah.
‪-So purple chips are yours?
‪I thought of not voting
‪for anyone yesterday.
‪Really?
‪Kyung-ho was very close to my ideal type,
‪so I guess I was really happy
‪that someone like that chose me.
‪It made me
‪think even more rashly.
‪This is how you walk in ballet.
‪Like that? No one can walk like that.
‪-We really walk like this.
‪-Really?
‪We get to see the ocean too.
‪-The ocean?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Cafe and ocean.
‪-So pretty.
‪-What is that?
‪Shall we dive in?
‪Should we take a selfie?
‪-Like this?
‪-Yeah, that's good.
‪-You're so funny.
‪One, two, three.
‪Let's go to the cafe now.
‪GA-YEON & KYUNG-HO
‪OUTPOST CAFE
‪I prepared this for you.
‪Thank you. I'm touched.
‪I pretended to be relaxed.
‪I pretend to be at ease
‪through my posture.
‪-I love a chair like this.
‪-This?
‪A chair with armrests.
‪I get a bit shy and freeze up at times,
‪and that's when I feel vulnerable.
‪Let's talk about each other.
‪Okay.
‪-What we're curious about.
‪-Okay.
‪What did you tell Hye-won?
‪-Your case worked on her, didn't it?
‪-My case?
‪I just told her that I wanted to
‪be clear about how I feel about you.
‪This is what I said.
‪"I'm going to follow your decision."
‪"I'll leave it to fate."
‪Did you really have no opinion?
‪You just went with who she chose?
‪Is that it?
‪No. To be honest,
‪it felt like if I went
‪on a date with Jung-min,
‪it'd be like we're a done deal.
‪But I thought I'd regret if that happened,
‪so I wanted to go on a date
‪with you today.
‪-Me too.
‪-So…
‪He's captivated by her.
‪-"Me too."
‪It's kind of like
‪he's being hypnotized.
‪"Do you like Ga-yeon?"
‪-"Me too."
‪-That's what it was like.
‪…on a date with you today.
‪-Me too.
‪-Which means
‪I got what I wanted.
‪You were the mastermind?
‪Yes.
‪Well, good for you.
‪You got what you wanted.
‪I'm not your first choice, right?
‪You just wanted to
‪have a conversation with me.
‪To be honest, I don't have a first choice
‪at the moment.
‪You thought it was Ye-rim, didn't you?
‪Yeah, totally.
‪When she told me her age,
‪she suddenly felt too young for me.
‪But regardless of that,
‪I wanted to chat with you.
‪I wanted to chat with you too.
‪Because your face
‪and overall physical appearance
‪are closest to my ideal type.
‪But you are the kind of guy
‪that I don't want to date.
‪Personality-wise?
‪No, because I feel strong attraction.
‪I want a relationship with someone
‪more mature who can keep me grounded.
‪And someone emotionally secure
‪who openly expresses their affection.
‪Kyung-ho isn't that kind of person.
‪He's someone who excites me.
‪I'm strongly attracted to you,
‪but I feel like I have to be careful.
‪-Well…
‪-This is what it is.
‪She's asked, "Do you want
‪a healthy, mild soup or spicy soup?"
‪And she goes, "I used to like
‪spicy soup when I was young,
‪but I have to care about
‪my health since I'm older,
‪so I want a healthy, mild soup."
‪That's exactly right.
‪Nicely put.
‪Then, what kind of person
‪do you think I am?
‪You don't date for long, do you?
‪No, I was in a long relationship
‪about twice.
‪Long from my standard.
‪The rest lasted about 100 days.
‪I felt like that's exactly
‪how you would date
‪based on what I've seen.
‪That I date just anybody?
‪-Is that what you're saying?
‪-No.
‪I promised myself that I would
‪date someone who is
‪grounded and mature, but slightly boring.
‪Why are you so extreme?
‪Can't you date someone
‪who is calm, mature, and fun?
‪That would be perfect.
‪But when I first saw you,
‪-you didn't seem that type.
‪-Okay.
‪But now you don't seem immature.
‪-Me?
‪-You seem grounded.
‪I try to be that way.
‪You're very popular.
‪Right now?
‪I wouldn't know.
‪But I do.
‪The most important thing for me
‪is who I like.
‪Never mind.
‪Should I make that second most important?
‪Maybe I'll focus on who likes me.
‪I think I was in
‪a more stable relationship
‪when the guy liked me more.
‪But the most memorable relationship
‪was with someone I liked more.
‪When I fall from someone at first sight,
‪I decide that I want to date that person
‪and I end up dating them.
‪-If I want him, I must have him.
‪-That's what you wanted to say.
‪-If you want something, you must have it?
‪-Yeah.
‪Of course you should.
‪-If I want to go out with him, I will.
‪-If you want to go out, you should.
‪Am I different from
‪your first impression of me?
‪You seemed a bit aloof and quiet.
‪-But do I seem different now?
‪-Yes.
‪-You're very talkative.
‪-I'm talkative. And?
‪And you laugh a lot too.
‪That's a good personality.
‪You have positive energy.
‪Once you talk to her, you realize Ga-yeon
‪is very different from what she seems.
‪She is full of cheerful
‪and positive energy.
‪He's right.
‪Ye-rim seems cheerful and cute,
‪-but she's calm and mature in person.
‪-Yeah.
‪Right.
‪I admire people with positive energy.
‪-You're also very…
‪-Yeah.
‪I'm really trying hard right now.
‪You're trying?
‪I've changed too.
‪I think people do change.
‪They want to take after what they admire.
‪-Yeah.
‪-When they want to become a certain way,
‪they end up changing like that.
‪I thought he would be a very playful,
‪funny, and energetic person.
‪But he was very calm.
‪The more I talked with him,
‪I realized he is very mature.
‪He's the same age as my younger brother.
‪I don't really develop
‪romantic feelings for younger guys,
‪but he was surprisingly mature
‪for his age.
‪-I have a younger brother.
‪-Right.
‪He's the same age as you.
‪When I think you're the same age
‪as my brother,
‪I'd assume you'd be immature.
‪But you're not. Why is that?
‪Because I dress like a grandma?
‪Maybe.
‪Are they digging for shellfish here?
‪I am curious.
‪I'm actually not that curious.
‪Are you curious?
‪No.
‪I started to feel like
‪I was gradually stirring up
‪her emotions more and more.
‪It didn't feel like
‪he was her clear first choice
‪and I was on the back burner.
‪-You have very big hands.
‪-Yeah, I have big hands.
‪Even your hands look like
‪those of someone in the arts.
‪Really?
‪I can play basic things like this
‪with both hands.
‪What are you doing with your hands?
‪Close your eyes.
‪What is it?
‪Sheep? No.
‪Yang?
‪No?
‪Hurry.
‪-Hwang?
‪-Nope.
‪-King?
‪-You're good though.
‪It was king.
‪I wrote "king" too.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪It wasn't "sheep." It was "king."
‪-What's your resolution for today?
‪-My resolution for today?
‪Man, she's really a player.
‪That's how you date someone.
‪What's your resolution for today?
‪-My resolution for today?
‪-Chae-rin.
‪The mudflat, here I come.
‪You got to be romantic yesterday.
‪We're clearly the comic relief.
‪Who knows?
‪We might get butterflies in our stomachs.
‪-I know.
‪-Watch out.
‪CHAE-RIN & JUNG-MIN
‪MINMEORU BEACH
‪You're in charge of the money today.
‪-Got it.
‪-There's not much to manage anyway.
‪-We only have 30,000 won.
‪-Yeah, 30,000 won.
‪We'll be in trouble if we lose
‪that 30,000 won. Got that?
‪-It's 10,000 won per person.
‪-That's two thirds of our budget.
‪-Wait, 20,000 on this? I'm shaking.
‪-Yeah.
‪The payment is complete.
‪REMAINING BUDGET: 10,000 WON
‪We have 10,000 won left now.
‪-Work gear?
‪-Okay.
‪-Aren't the baskets too small?
‪-Yeah, they're too small for our goal.
‪I think this mudflat is too small too.
‪THE MUDFLAT IS TOO SMALL FOR THEM
‪I think it's too small for our goal.
‪-What is this?
‪-What?
‪-Wait.
‪-Hey.
‪-It's hard to even move.
‪-Seriously?
‪Look at you walk.
‪I didn't poop my pants, Jung-min.
‪-Are you ready, Min?
‪-Of course, Rin!
‪-There's something there.
‪-There is.
‪I found one!
‪-Wow!
‪-Wait.
‪-It's just a shell.
‪-No, it's not.
‪-It's not!
‪-Yeah?
‪I got one.
‪-Awesome.
‪-Our first catch.
‪Yay!
‪They're all here.
‪-You can just scrape them up.
‪-I know.
‪-This is fun. Scraping them up with hands.
‪-Yeah.
‪Jung-min.
‪I think I'm stuck.
‪-I'll pull you out.
‪-Wait.
‪PRESSING DOWN
‪PRESSING DOWN ONE MORE TIME
‪-I'm even more stuck.
‪-Unbelievable. I know.
‪Both my feet are stuck now!
‪I got out.
‪It's pretty deep.
‪SIGHING
‪-Jung-min.
‪-Yeah?
‪Are we really on a date?
‪Finding love is supposed to be this hard?
‪A sea worm. It's quite big.
‪SHE HEARS A COUPLE LAUGHING NEARBY
‪-How gross.
‪-They seem so happy over there.
‪They're wearing matching T-shirts.
‪-They are?
‪-Yeah, and we are too.
‪How do ours match?
‪The pants.
‪How?
‪COUPLE NEARBY KEEPS GIGGLING
‪THEY KEEP HEARING THE HAPPY COUPLE
‪Doesn't it seem like
‪they're digging up a lot?
‪They keep screaming.
‪We're competing with them.
‪Hurry up and find them.
‪Here's one.
‪-Woo!
‪This is embarrassing.
‪-I know.
‪-Let's not do it.
‪-Watching those two makes me happy.
‪-Yeah.
‪-It'd be nice to see a spark between them.
‪-I know.
‪-Want to make a bet?
‪-What kind of bet?
‪The amount.
‪Man, I would've put
‪even the small ones in then.
‪-Give the other person Heart Chips?
‪-The Heart Chips?
‪Give me Heart Chips,
‪this many.
‪I'm not going home then.
‪-Go!
‪-Oh, no! My feet!
‪THE HEART CHIP WAGER IS ON
‪I should run away.
‪Don't follow me.
‪Have you lost your mind?
‪-I have an ax.
‪-Okay.
‪You're scary.
‪SNEAKILY
‪There are spots with a lot of them.
‪STEALS
‪You didn't take any, did you?
‪Are you insane?
‪You can't trust anybody.
‪I found one.
‪Awesome.
‪Why aren't there any here?
‪I can't see any.
‪Me neither.
‪Are you saying you can't find any
‪while digging them up?
‪Don't dig there.
‪Hey, it's a jackpot here!
‪There are two here.
‪No.
‪Hey, putting them in for now.
‪Sorry.
‪-Jeez. Go away.
‪-Come on.
‪-Wow!
‪-What?
‪Jackpot.
‪Are you okay?
‪It's so big.
‪Done.
‪THE SHELLFISH DIGGING CHALLENGE
‪FOR HEART CHIPS IS OVER
‪-Let's count them.
‪-Okay.
‪-Let's count each other's basket.
‪-Each other's?
‪FAIR AND SQUARE
‪-Discard the broken ones.
‪-I'll start counting.
‪Three, four.
‪Forty.
‪CAREFULLY
‪Ten… Fifty.
‪-You've got 56.
‪-It's 55.
‪You dug up a lot.
‪Sixty-three.
‪You're going to give me 63 Heart Chips?
‪Will you be okay with that?
‪I mean, that's what we agreed on.
‪-You have to give them to me.
‪-Okay.
‪Yes!
‪-What a shame.
‪-What do you mean?
‪I was hoping to be king.
‪It's tough.
‪Jjajangmyeon‪ is best
‪after a long day's work.
‪Gosh, it's so cheap.
‪JJAJANGMYEON, 3,000 WON
‪What do you want?
‪-We have no choice.
‪-Right, we don't.
‪Let's get two of that.
‪How much do we have left?
‪We'll have 4,000 won left.
‪-Erguotou.
‪-4,000 won.
‪-That'll come to 10,000 won.
‪-Money well spent.
‪USED UP 30,000 WON
‪Hey, 56%?
‪-I'm going to drink.
‪-Me too.
‪Water.
‪There's a water dispenser.
‪-Here. Mix it.
‪-Okay.
‪I like it. It warms me up.
‪My tongue is numb.
‪-You drank it up in one go.
‪-My tongue is numb.
‪-Enjoy.
‪-It's so delicious.
‪-Yeah, it's good.
‪It's really the old school ‪jjajangmyeon‪.
‪It's really tasty.
‪Cheers.
‪Take small sips.
‪The smell faded.
‪No, it didn't. Gosh.
‪I did it.
‪Man, the smell.
‪Did you have a second choice?
‪-Second choice?
‪-Yeah.
‪-I didn't have one.
‪-Right?
‪I could tell.
‪-Ga-yeon is--
‪-But you left a good first impression.
‪What? Really?
‪-You were the first one I saw, right?
‪-Yeah.
‪You see,
‪the way you talked and reacted
‪wasn't so over-the-top,
‪like, just enough.
‪I did think that.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪-So?
‪-What?
‪Why did you go for Ga-yeon, then?
‪Well, that happened yesterday.
‪-You chose her on the first day too.
‪-That's right.
‪That was because Kyung-ho chose Ye-rim,
‪and you had something going on too.
‪-Okay.
‪-Because of those things,
‪I went to Ga-yeon.
‪How do you think Ga-yeon feels?
‪I think she is most interested in me.
‪-You feel it?
‪-Yeah.
‪We spent time together.
‪You move around the house, right?
‪The path she tends to take?
‪-What is that?
‪-I feel like
‪-we follow each other around.
‪-You?
‪I follow Ga-yeon around,
‪-and she follows me around.
‪-How cute.
‪Her feelings for me are the biggest.
‪Do you have confidence
‪in one another?
‪I think so.
‪We talked about it too.
‪Do you think Ga-yeon has a second choice?
‪I think so.
‪Who?
‪I don't know.
‪Who's your second choice?
‪That's a secret.
‪Between us?
‪-The shellfish digging duo?
‪I came here with you today, right?
‪It was fun.
‪I had fun too.
‪Seriously though, after today,
‪I did think that you are
‪a really good person.
‪I'm serious.
‪-Come on, guys.
‪-You know what?
‪They'll start dating after the show
‪and leave everyone in shock.
‪They get along well.
‪Feelings might develop later on.
‪Who do you think will become king?
‪-Ga-yeon.
‪-Why?
‪She is many guys' second choice,
‪so I think she'll get
‪a lot of votes from the men.
‪Who knows?
‪Ga-yeon's date may have gone well today.
‪That is possible.
‪How do you feel?
‪It would be shocking
‪if her first choice changed.
‪-Would it really be shocking?
‪-Yeah.
‪-I doubt that will happen, though.
‪-Okay.
‪I don't think it will change.
‪I'm sure it won't.
‪HYE-WON & HA-YOON
‪Let's go.
‪Aren't you driving too fast?
‪I'm so happy.
‪-I'm so excited.
‪-Me too.
‪The reason why the algorithm
‪keeps suggesting it is--
‪Darn it.
‪-Wrong turn.
‪-It's okay.
‪I shouldn't go this way.
‪We got in the car, but I was nervous,
‪so I kept making the wrong turn.
‪Should I be quiet
‪until we get to the coastal road?
‪Yeah. Hush.
‪So I told him to be quiet.
‪I couldn't focus.
‪-Let's not talk.
‪-Okay.
‪Let's talk a lot
‪-when you don't have to drive.
‪-Yeah.
‪I'll be quiet.
‪I have to focus.
‪Ha-yoon said sorry and just stayed still.
‪But then he started talking again.
‪What a fun start.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Are you okay? I mean, driving.
‪-I'm fine with driving.
‪-There's a lot to focus on.
‪But I don't think I can talk.
‪-I'll let you focus.
‪-Oh my gosh.
‪Actually, I can't multitask.
‪Can we make it back home today?
‪We'll be doing ceramic painting.
‪What will you do?
‪-There's a teddy bear.
‪-There are so many options.
‪I love teddy bears.
‪Can you drink
‪the hot-and-cold drink in this?
‪Hot-and-cold drink?
‪-Drink it in this.
‪-Do you really want me to drink it?
‪-Do you really want me to do that?
‪-You can drink from this.
‪Maybe it'll be too difficult.
‪What should we draw?
‪I don't think about it before I begin.
‪Do you
‪have someone besides me
‪that you're interested in?
‪To be honest, there's no one.
‪Well, we'll have to talk more today,
‪but the more I talk with you,
‪you have many qualities that I like.
‪You have a lot of qualities
‪that I find attractive.
‪For me,
‪there's no one else right now.
‪I want to ask you the same question.
‪Are you curious?
‪Yes, I am curious.
‪-I'll let you know.
‪-Hello.
‪THE WORKSHOP TOOLS ARRIVE
‪When I told her
‪my first choice has already been decided
‪and I am not interested in anyone else,
‪the instructor showed up,
‪so I wasn't able to ask her that question.
‪-Yes, thank you.
‪-Okay.
‪-Your answer…
‪-Right.
‪You must wonder. I'll tell you.
‪-Later?
‪-I have something to tell you too.
‪Okay. Me too.
‪-We have to decide what to draw first.
‪-Yeah.
‪When I talk with you,
‪my voice becomes very relaxed
‪and it becomes softer too.
‪Really?
‪It's interesting.
‪-You feel relaxed, right?
‪-Yeah, I do.
‪That's what matters.
‪-This is harder than I expected.
‪-Yeah.
‪I'm drawing this while thinking of you.
‪Of course, I have something in mind too.
‪-This is so pretty.
‪-It's like a piece of art.
‪You're good.
‪It looks really dumb but cute.
‪-I want to see it up close.
‪-Let me explain it.
‪There's a meaning to it. And it's obvious.
‪-Wait, I know what it is.
‪-Right.
‪It's you, me, and the others.
‪Yeah.
‪You always say that you're calm, right?
‪I feel like you're slowly
‪rubbing off on me.
‪So that's what I tried to portray.
‪One, two, three.
‪HYE-WON & HA-YOON
‪OSTERIA FONTANA
‪-Let's enjoy our meal.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Thank you.
‪Oh my.
‪It looks delicious.
‪It's so good.
‪-It's tasty.
‪-It is?
‪Let's continue what we were
‪talking about.
‪May I ask you?
‪Did you know that I already knew Kyung-ho?
‪-You knew?
‪-Yeah.
‪Because I like dance so much,
‪I already knew Kyung-ho.
‪So I was curious about him.
‪But I realized it was just as a fan.
‪It wasn't something romantic with him.
‪I was able to confirm that,
‪so I'm not interested in anyone else.
‪So,
‪you're the only one for me now.
‪It’s been a really long time
‪since someone looked me
‪in the eyes calmly and sincerely say,
‪"I want to go
‪on a date with you."
‪I want to go on a date with you.
‪That's how I feel.
‪-That sounds good.
‪-Yeah.
‪Okay, that has been
‪registered in my head.
‪I was very sleepy and exhausted,
‪but I was so deeply moved by that.
‪And I saw a spark in his eyes too.
‪It was so bright.
‪-It was so touching.
‪-Really?
‪But wasn't I really unkempt?
‪It was the best line to me.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪Gosh, jeez…
‪What's wrong? Are you feeling shy?
‪I think I am feeling shy.
‪The way you were able to talk about that
‪with such sincerity, but without making it
‪pushy or overwhelming…
‪My heart skipped a beat.
‪Cheers.
‪Am I blushing?
‪Not really.
‪To me, Hye-won sparkles.
‪For one thing, her eyes are so big
‪that they sparkle.
‪Because she bounces
‪from one subject to another,
‪she may come across as rambling
‪or a little all over the place.
‪But when she talks about
‪something she knows
‪and feels strongly about,
‪her eyes sparkle with confidence.
‪He seems to accommodate me in every way.
‪When I'm talking about something,
‪he would go along with my conversation.
‪I love that so much.
‪I feel like my feelings for him
‪are gradually getting stronger.
‪Thank you for coming on a date with me.
‪Well, I wanted to come.
‪Okay.
‪That's a shame.
‪Ha-yoon and Hye-won seem like they're set.
‪That's why it's a shame.
‪I wanted to give it a shot at him.
‪YE-RIM & DO-GEON
‪PORK MOUNTAIN
‪Hey, there's a dog.
‪-Awesome.
‪-No way.
‪It's waiting so patiently.
‪What a sweet dog.
‪-It's waiting for us.
‪-I know.
‪Come here.
‪No way.
‪Come over here.
‪Where did you go? Come here.
‪Hello.
‪How adorable.
‪Look at its eyes. Looks so smart.
‪I'll start grilling.
‪Do you trust me?
‪Of course.
‪-It looks good.
‪-It does.
‪-Now that I see it…
‪-I know.
‪It looks good.
‪Try one.
‪Is it hot?
‪-It's tasty.
‪-Is it?
‪-Would you like a wrap?
‪-That would be nice.
‪Nice wrap.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Was it good?
‪-It's good.
‪It's all done.
‪Thank you.
‪-Shall we clink our glasses?
‪-Yes.
‪-What if
‪-Yeah?
‪Chae-rin's mind changed today?
‪Do you still want to
‪go out with her tomorrow?
‪-Of course.
‪-Really?
‪If she changed her mind today,
‪I can--
‪Change it back tomorrow?
‪I have to change it back.
‪That's all the more reason
‪to go on a date with her tomorrow.
‪If she changed her mind…
‪Not me.
‪If they like someone more than me…
‪It could be because he's not
‪spending time with you today.
‪-You're right.
‪-Yeah.
‪-You never know.
‪Okay. I want to go out
‪with Kyung-ho tomorrow too.
‪Yeah, you should win him back
‪when you go on that date.
‪You can't change a guy's mind.
‪Why do you think that?
‪Speaking from experience.
‪I talked to Ga-yeon
‪-while we were outside.
‪-In the tent?
‪Kyung-ho came and pulled Ga-yeon aside
‪to have a chat with her.
‪You said earlier that he didn't!
‪He did.
‪Really?
‪-Briefly.
‪-And?
‪So…
‪That's the first time Ga-yeon knew.
‪Knew what?
‪That Kyung-ho is…
‪-Curious about her?
‪-Yeah, that he's curious about her.
‪That's when she first found out.
‪All right, then.
‪I don't think she had any interest in him
‪until then.
‪-You're wrong.
‪-I'm wrong?
‪-You got it all wrong.
‪-I did?
‪Totally wrong.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪I can see that Kyung-ho
‪is curious about Ga-yeon,
‪and I can see
‪Ga-yeon reacting to that too.
‪-I see.
‪-Totally.
‪I'm so curious how it will go today.
‪I'm curious,
‪but I also don't want to find out.
‪I'm curious but afraid.
‪-Scared of getting hurt?
‪-Yeah.
‪Yeah.
‪-I get you.
‪-What do I do if I get hurt?
‪Are you going to give up
‪without even trying,
‪or are you going to try and get hurt?
‪If it were you,
‪you would try to change Chae-rin's mind
‪even if she chose someone else.
‪I have to change her mind.
‪Where do you get that kind of courage?
‪Why not?
‪Should I give up then?
‪-You do have a point.
‪-Yeah.
‪That makes no sense.
‪You like him.
‪I like him, but he doesn't like me back.
‪But it's not like that person
‪wasn't interested in you at all.
‪-You're right.
‪-Yeah.
‪If she wasn't interested in me at all
‪from the start,
‪I wouldn't want to
‪force my feelings on her.
‪-You wouldn't?
‪-But you see,
‪things were going well between us,
‪so if she starts straying,
‪I have to get her back.
‪You should have
‪a real conversation with him tonight.
‪I hope they get back before we do.
‪Why?
‪That way, it'll be easier
‪to feel their vibe
‪when we get back.
‪I can see if they are sitting
‪next to each other and things like that.
‪I was really hoping
‪that Kyung-ho and Ga-yeon
‪would be back before us.
‪If they came late,
‪it would mean they had fun.
‪When I look at Ye-rim,
‪I see myself in her. I'm like that too.
‪I'd be like, "It's because I'm too young."
‪It's so frustrating
‪that I don't want to do that anymore.
‪There's no need to be like that.
‪I really miss Chae-rin.
‪What do I do?
‪Me too.
‪Jeez.
‪Are you going to tell her
‪when you get back?
‪That you missed her?
‪Is that how close you are?
‪I could if I wanted to.
‪You should say it too.
‪I could if I wanted to as well.
‪Yeah, you could if you wanted to.
‪I wonder how many are back.
‪Me too.
‪Oh, there's something I want to ask you.
‪What is it?
‪Never mind.
‪Come on. Tell me.
‪Ga-yeon got ‪chojang‪ on her sleeve.
‪Chojang.
‪That's cute.
‪Who did you vote for yesterday?
‪Who did I vote for?
‪Right now,
‪there are only two people that I have
‪romantic interest in.
‪Who are they?
‪You and Jung-min.
‪-See? You don't avoid my eye contact.
‪-Huh?
‪Most people do.
‪My mom told me that
‪it's rude to avoid eye contact
‪and that I should look at them
‪when you talk to them.
‪Do you do that to everyone?
‪-Oh, in here?
‪-Yeah.
‪No, not really.
‪Didn't our eyes meet quite often?
‪-Us?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Right?
‪I must've been looking at you a lot.
‪-Really?
‪-Well,
‪didn't you say that
‪-your gaze kept drifting toward me?
‪-Yeah.
‪I must've been like that too.
‪It was like that for me too.
‪When I look at someone,
‪I don't avoid eye contact.
‪But he looks into my eyes
‪longer than I look at his.
‪When our eyes locked,
‪my heart skipped a beat.
‪He captivates me.
‪My heart
‪kind of skipped a beat.
‪They said the same thing.
‪I love this.
‪"Skipped a beat."
‪I could feel butterflies in my stomach.
‪All the constellations show up like this.
‪Then, you find your star sign.
‪I was kind of in a daze.
‪It was pretty hot in the car too.
‪It felt like I was moving like this
‪while we were talking,
‪so I don't even remember what I said.
‪-The Big Dipper?
‪-Yeah, the Big Dipper.
‪And?
‪How I feel for you has become clearer.
‪I don't know exactly when,
‪but it became clear before I knew it.
‪It felt like the things that weighed on me
‪were finally lifted.
‪I felt released.
‪Who do you want to go out with tomorrow?
‪The date?
‪I think I'll go out with you.
‪Really? You think you will?
‪Yeah.
‪How?
‪The king will make it happen.
‪Who's the king?
‪Me?
‪You?
‪Who would you like to be king?
‪Me?
‪You?
‪That way, I can find out how you feel.
‪I don't want to ask you directly.
‪But I do want to know.
‪Of course, I want to know how you feel.
‪But I don't want to ask you upfront.
‪Not yet.
‪Who you end up choosing
‪may make me sad or happy. Who knows?
‪I think my head is going to hurt now.
‪You're going to sigh 30 to 50 times.
‪I'm going to be a depressed Ga-yeon.
‪Depressed Ga-yeon?
‪When do I have to make up my mind
‪and let you know?
‪You aren't sure yet?
‪I think I know how I feel now.
‪You went on a date with both women.
‪That's right. I have.
‪I've only gone out with you.
‪That's right.
‪When your mind is made up,
‪will you tell Ye-rim or me?
‪It may not be right away,
‪but I'll say it as soon as I can.
‪You already went
‪-on two dates.
‪-I went on two dates.
‪You may have a lot of time, but I…
‪All right.
‪-Why can't I see their hands?
‪-What's that angle?
‪-You should've lowered it.
‪-Yeah.
‪I can't see even from this angle.
‪This is driving me crazy.
‪You may have a lot of time, but I…
‪All right.
‪I get it.
‪It would be nice if we could
‪go out again tomorrow.
‪No?
‪Do what your heart tells you.
‪If you can go on a date
‪with Jung-min tomorrow,
‪it wouldn't be a bad idea to go.
‪I'd be sad and in pain,
‪and I'd want to punch him,
‪but…
‪Who knows? I may not like you tomorrow.
‪I'm just kidding.
‪In a way,
‪I feel like
‪I'm casually seeing two people.
‪Doesn't it feel very bizarre?
‪Yeah, but I'm not in a place
‪where I can make a decision yet
‪because I haven't had
‪a conversation like this with Jung-min.
‪Do it today.
‪-How?
‪-Well,
‪have a long conversation today.
‪Find a place to do it.
‪I don't know.
‪From the start, what if I…
‪From the very start, when we arrived…
‪what if I were only interested in you,
‪only talked to you,
‪only looked at you,
‪said, "I only want to go out with you…"
‪and held your hand and stuff?
‪Would things have been different?
‪Yeah, completely.
‪That was
‪huge for me.
‪At first, I wasn't interested in Jung-min
‪at all.
‪So that played a huge part.
‪Yeah, holding hands was
‪very big for me.
‪It really was.
‪I didn't expect it at all.
‪CHAE-RIN AND JUNG-MIN ARE BACK
‪THE SHELLFISH THEY DUG UP
‪I feel like we have too many.
‪THEY SOAK THEM AS SOON AS THEY GET BACK
‪-Done.
‪-Good.
‪I wonder how the date
‪will affect the Heart Chip vote today.
‪I wonder who will become king.
‪-I'm curious.
‪-I have to be king.
‪YE-RIM AND DO-GEON ARRIVE
‪-Look at the stars.
‪-Where?
‪Look at the stars and make a wish.
‪I made mine.
‪-What did you wish for?
‪-I wished for things to work out well.
‪-Hahaha.
‪You're a romantic boy.
‪-What if no one's here?
‪-Right?
‪-What?
‪You're back.
‪-Did you have fun?
‪-Did you?
‪-Me?
‪-Yeah.
‪I guess I had fun.
‪-Was the barbecue good?
‪-Yeah.
‪-He's asleep.
‪It was totally…
‪First of all…
‪BRIEFING ON THE INFO SHE GATHERED
‪Do-geon is totally into you.
‪Should I put it that way?
‪-He totally is.
‪-His first choice?
‪You're totally his first choice.
‪Surprisingly, his second choice
‪-is Ga-yeon.
‪-What?
‪His ideal type is someone talkative.
‪Someone who is bubbly?
‪-So--
‪-For real?
‪I had no idea.
‪He said he's interested in two people,
‪and Ga-yeon is his second choice.
‪So he said when he had to choose
‪who to go to the tent with,
‪he was actually glad
‪that Ga-yeon was able to go.
‪-He was actually glad?
‪-He was glad.
‪-Because he hadn't talked to her before.
‪-Really?
‪I wasn't bothered that he chose Ga-yeon
‪since they didn't have much interaction.
‪So I wasn't fazed at all. I didn't care.
‪But I found out Ga-yeon
‪was his second choice.
‪He said he didn't choose me
‪because he thought
‪I wouldn't want to stay in the tent.
‪I was very touched by that then.
‪But it turns out, that jerk was…
‪I had no idea.
‪I had absolutely no idea either.
‪After he talked with her,
‪he said he isn't curious
‪about her anymore.
‪After talking with her?
‪He said since tomorrow's date
‪may be the last one,
‪he definitely wants to go out with you.
‪He even said that he is a little bothered
‪about you going on a date with Jung-min.
‪Really?
‪FEELING BETTER
‪When I asked what he would do
‪if Chae-rin changed her mind,
‪he said he would change it back tomorrow.
‪-What a man.
‪-Right?
‪-Tomorrow may be our last.
‪-Date?
‪-Yes. Then I want to go with Kyung-ho.
‪-You want to go with Kyung-ho?
‪But you don't know
‪how he feels after today.
‪I really have no clue.
‪We are going to chat today anyway.
‪Make me king.
‪Because today, I…
‪-Hi.
‪-Hey.
‪THE KING HAS RETURNED
‪-Did you just get back?
‪-Yeah.
‪Did you enjoy your date? Was it okay?
‪-Yeah, totally.
‪-Yeah, it was fun.
‪Thanks to you.
‪THE KING GOES TO THE BATHROOM
‪What were we talking about?
‪-What were we talking about?
‪-Oh, making you…
‪Did you have a chat with Jung-min?
‪We went to the mudflat, right?
‪Is he here?
‪We made a bet.
‪We agreed to give the winner
‪Heart Chips for the amount dug up.
‪-And I dug up over 60 shellfish.
‪-Okay.
‪-He'll definitely give them to you?
‪-Over 60. Yeah.
‪Then, I'll concentrate
‪my votes on you too.
‪I didn't use that many Heart Chips,
‪so I have 237 left.
‪How can you concentrate yours on mine?
‪I can give you
‪about 200.
‪Wait, but we can only vote
‪for the guys, right?
‪You're right. What the heck?
‪You're so cute.
‪Either me or Ga-yeon
‪will become king today.
‪We have to keep her in check.
‪DO-GEON ENTERS
‪I won the bet today.
‪I dug up over 60 shellfish.
‪Do you see how hard I tried?
‪Do you see it?
‪I love things like this.
‪-This is what we want to see.
‪-Yeah.
‪This is what I wanted.
‪The two should go to the tent today!
‪Please let them go to the tent. I beg you!
‪Do you see how hard I tried?
‪Do you see it?
‪My wrist hurts.
‪My wrist hurts because of you.
‪Why?
‪-Are you trying to be king?
‪-I don't know.
‪You worked hard to be king, didn't you?
‪No, I don't know.
‪How was last night?
‪The beds in the tent were very close.
‪We talked about this and that,
‪and then, I went to sleep first.
‪What?
‪Nothing.
‪When I ran into Do-geon,
‪I felt my heart skip a beat.
‪Is it because he's tall?
‪When I see someone tall like you,
‪it fascinates me.
‪You were with
‪someone taller than me today.
‪I did.
‪-I did.
‪-You did.
‪MEANWHILE, YE-RIM IS ALONE
‪I wondered when
‪Kyung-ho and Ga-yeon would be back.
‪I wondered what kind of relationship
‪they would be in now.
‪I was worried
‪about how much their feelings developed
‪and how much they've shared.
‪When will they get back?
‪So what if they come back?
‪"Did you have fun?"
‪What do you think I should say?
‪sounds too confrontational, no?
‪SHE SEES KYUNG-HO'S REFLECTION
‪He's back.
‪Let's pretend we're having a fun chat.
‪Gosh.
‪-Did you have fun? Just got back?
‪-Yeah.
‪-You got back very late.
‪Did you go far?
‪We did go far.
‪-I see.
‪-Yeah.
‪-You're back.
‪-How was it?
‪-I'm exhausted.
‪-How was it, Kyung-ho?
‪-Me? I had fun.
‪I had fun. Yeah.
‪Was there a change of heart?
‪Me?
‪Of course.
‪I think things have become clear.
‪If I told you, you'd tell Ye-rim, right?
‪What do you mean?
‪Maybe not? Is it just my assumption?
‪I'm afraid you're secret allies.
‪It doesn't matter if she finds out.
‪What I wanted to do
‪was sort out my feelings for Ga-yeon.
‪I mean, I wanted clarity
‪on how I feel about her.
‪I got clarity for sure.
‪And with a little more time,
‪it'll become even clearer.
‪Also, I plan on talking with Ye-rim
‪one more time
‪and with Ga-yeon too, if we have time.
‪Today?
‪I think so.
‪Things will become more certain
‪for everyone tomorrow.
‪It may become certain for some,
‪and not for others,
‪but I think it will for me pretty soon.
‪AFTER THEIR CONVERSATION ENDS
‪-Oh, you're back.
‪-Hi.
‪Hi there.
‪YE-RIM COMES TO SEE DO-GEON IMMEDIATELY
‪Which one's mine?
‪I heard him out a bit.
‪Stop dilly-dallying.
‪I haven't heard it quite clearly either.
‪ANOTHER PERSON IS LISTENING
‪I think you may have a chance too.
‪-Do a good job of charming him.
‪-What did he say?
‪Well,
‪-he was very ambiguous.
‪-What did he say?
‪He said he asked Ga-yeon out on a date
‪because he was curious,
‪not because he has
‪strong feelings for her.
‪He thought his mind will be made up
‪after talking with her today.
‪But he said he'll have a chat
‪with both of you today.
‪With me and Ga-yeon?
‪But he said his mind is
‪pretty much made up already.
‪I think you have a better chance.
‪I'm so proud of you, Do-geon.
‪Try to win him over
‪when you talk with him.
‪Do-geon said that it could be me,
‪so I was honestly feeling very happy.
‪I'm just saying you have a shot.
‪Thank you so much.
‪Man, this is driving me crazy.
‪Just sit still!
‪How can the wires get crossed like this?
‪I think what Kyung-ho meant is
‪that he'll talk to Ye-rim to end things.
‪Ye-rim is too fickle too.
‪Just because she heard that, she goes…
‪I get it, though.
‪-Is this mine?
‪-Yeah.
‪Let's clink our glasses.
‪Cheers.
‪-Isn't it good?
‪-Yeah.
‪What did you have for dinner?
‪Grilled shellfish and raw fish.
‪That must've been good.
‪-Ours was good too.
‪-Yeah, it was.
‪The barbecue was good too.
‪If everyone enjoyed their date,
‪the king is happy.
‪Time to be dethroned.
‪I liked it too.
‪To be by the king.
‪-I liked being close to power.
‪-How nice for him.
‪Like a scheming advisor?
‪Yeah, like a scheming advisor.
‪The mudflat was nice too.
‪Chae-rin used the hoe like this.
‪Pow!
‪Then, the blood would…
‪Wait, not the blood.
‪It's a mudflat.
‪Did you only dig up shellfish?
‪-We didn't dig up love.
‪-Oh, how sad.
‪I see.
‪We have to go together.
‪-We have to go now.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Go where?
‪-Where?
‪Only the male tenants.
‪THE MEN'S DAY 3 HEART CHIP VOTE BEGINS
‪PARK JUNG-MIN
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪Multiple votes are allowed again today,
‪and Black Heart Chips
‪can be exchanged for Heart Chips.
‪Since I lost the bet…
‪I did briefly think of
‪betraying her,
‪but I gave them to her in the end.
‪I accepted my defeat
‪and gave her exactly 63 hearts.
‪I hope Ga-yeon becomes king.
‪Why?
‪When we talked today…
‪Well, I can't share more.
‪It's about Ga-yeon's feelings.
‪Anyway, I hope she becomes king.
‪JUNG-MIN IS WRITING ANOTHER MESSAGE
‪I wrote, "I'm rooting for the king"
‪and put it in her box
‪because I felt like Ga-yeon
‪would become king.
‪PARK JUNG-MIN COMPLETED VOTING
‪63 TO CHAE-RIN, 16 TO GA-YEON
‪Did you have fun, Ga-yeon?
‪What did you do?
‪We went to a cafe.
‪Then, we had grilled shellfish.
‪Why did it take so long?
‪You guys were the last to come.
‪Your hand is a mess.
‪Tomorrow's date?
‪I'd love to go out.
‪There's someone I want to go out with too.
‪You know who you want to go out with?
‪-Who I want to go out with?
‪-Yeah.
‪Yeah, but it's a secret.
‪JUNG HA-YOON
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪My mind is pretty set.
‪WE TALKED A LOT AND I GOT TO LEARN MORE
‪ABOUT YOU ON OUR DATE. THANK YOU
‪HA-YOON GAVE HYE-WON 66 HEARTS
‪JUNG HA-YOON COMPLETED VOTING
‪66 HEARTS TO HYE-WON
‪PARK DO-GEON
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪HE EXCHANGED THEM WITH BLACK HEART CHIPS
‪I wanted to help Ye-rim.
‪If Kyung-ho becomes king,
‪he would take Ga-yeon on a date,
‪so I gave him the Black Heart Chips
‪to eliminate that possibility.
‪I gave my Heart Chips to Chae-rin.
‪YES, I WAS HERE
‪I thought that the "Yes" on the note
‪from the second day
‪was from Chae-rin.
‪PARK DO-GEON COMPLETED VOTING
‪24 TO CHAE-RIN, 23 BLACK TO KYUNG-HO
‪Why did it take so long?
‪I was thinking it over.
‪Really?
‪Man, I was so torn.
‪Were you thinking
‪about how much to give me?
‪What did you say?
‪-What?
‪-Nothing.
‪Who did you vote for?
‪Can you not tell me?
‪I don't have many hearts left.
‪I used up too many yesterday.
‪I'd better use a lot today.
‪My hands are cold.
‪She feels uneasy.
‪-Ga-yeon feels uneasy.
‪-Yeah.
‪She has a lot on her mind right now.
‪How is it so cold?
‪It's because I was outside.
‪How is it? Aren't I like a hand warmer?
‪I run hot.
‪KANG KYUNG-HO
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪How many do I have?
‪I put them in Ga-yeon's box.
‪It was a very huge number for me.
‪It meant, "I had fun today. This is
‪how strong my feelings for you are."
‪But it also meant,
‪"I hope you become king."
‪The king can do whatever they like.
‪I was hoping she could do
‪what she wants in the end.
‪That's why I did it.
‪HE IS IN DEEP THOUGHT
‪AFTER VOTING FOR GA-YEON
‪KANG KYUNG-HO COMPLETED VOTING
‪???
‪THEY ARE BUSY PLAYING GONGGI
‪He's back.
‪-You took a very long time.
‪-Why did it take so long?
‪I'm cold.
‪THE FEMALE TENANTS MAY COME OUT
‪AND ENTER THE HEART ROOM NOW
‪-Let's go.
‪-Wait for me.
‪You should get changed.
‪I can't.
‪Then, wear this at least.
‪-Like this.
‪-I'll wear this.
‪Do you have a puffer jacket?
‪I think I can just wrap this around me.
‪It's over there.
‪GA-YEON WRAPS
‪KYUNG-HO'S JACKET AROUND HER WAIST
‪Did the rule change?
‪We aren't going one by one.
‪MOON CHAE-RIN
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪Because I realized the Heart Chips
‪aren't just for expressing my feelings,
‪how I use them became
‪all the more important.
‪We keep encountering
‪unexpected turn of events,
‪so I wondered if there may come a time
‪where I have to use a lot of Heart Chips.
‪TIME TO GO ON A DATE WITH ME
‪That's why I only used one.
‪Since I did have to express how I felt.
‪MOON CHAE-RIN COMPLETED VOTING
‪ONE HEART TO DO-GEON
‪JUNG HYE-WON
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪To Ha-yoon…
‪Because he is the man
‪who made my day today…
‪THANK YOU
‪JUNG HYE-WON COMPLETED VOTING
‪9 HEARTS TO HA-YOON
‪So far, my first choice hasn't changed.
‪I said I was confused whether
‪my feelings for Kyung-ho
‪were romantic or platonic, right?
‪I think it's romantic.
‪-You got to confirm it.
‪-My head hurts more.
‪-I think it'll get harder for me.
‪-Did you have a headache all day?
‪But so far, it's still Jung-min.
‪Who makes your heart flutter more?
‪I'm sure it's Kyung-ho.
‪No? Sorry.
‪I think it's still Jung-min.
‪But I haven't even
‪gone on a date with Jung-min yet.
‪I'll know when I go on a date
‪with Jung-min.
‪That's when my feelings will become clear.
‪Then, I should tell one of them
‪as soon as I figure it out.
‪I'd have to tell them who my choice is.
‪She makes it seem like
‪she decided on Jung-min,
‪but things keep happening with Kyung-ho.
‪It seems like she admitted
‪that she has romantic feelings for him.
‪Kyung-ho is practically her first choice.
‪If I were Jung-min,
‪I would be so disappointed in her.
‪But when you think about it,
‪Ga-yeon did nothing wrong.
‪Wait.
‪-She didn't do anything wrong, but…
‪-When I think about it,
‪she didn't do anything wrong.
‪-She didn't do anything wrong, but…
‪-Yeah.
‪I think Ga-yeon is sincere
‪about Jung-min too.
‪I don't know. This is hard.
‪-Let's watch.
‪-Yeah, let's watch.
‪PARK GA-YEON
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪LET'S HAVE FUN TOMORROW
‪I HAD FUN TODAY!
‪I wanted to go on a date with him,
‪so I thought we can go on our date
‪if I make Jung-min king.
‪GA-YEON GAVE JUNG-MIN
‪163 HEARTS
‪And since I had fun
‪on my date with Kyung-ho,
‪I made that known to him.
‪PARK GA-YEON COMPLETED VOTING
‪163 TO JUNG-MIN, 6 TO KYUNG-HO
‪She gave 163.
‪That's her sealing the deal.
‪LEE YE-RIM
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪SHE HAS THE UNUSED 10 BLACK HEART CHIPS
‪FROM YESTERDAY
‪I gave all the black ones I had left
‪into Ga-yeon's box.
‪YE-RIM GAVE KYUNG-HO
‪11 HEARTS
‪LEE YE-RIM COMPLETED VOTING
‪11 TO KYUNG-HO, 10 BLACK HEARTS TO GA-YEON
‪The Heart Chip vote
‪for the third day has ended.
‪YE-RIM CAME TO SEE DO-GEON AFTER VOTING
‪He went to change his pants.
‪Talk to him when he comes out.
‪Talk to him before the results are out?
‪Talking to him after the results are out
‪won't make any difference, will it?
‪-You know, I want…
‪-Already--
‪I want him to want me.
‪Oh, no.
‪Is it her age that's the issue?
‪I think her age and lack of experience
‪are the issue.
‪They have to be on a similar page
‪for sparks to fly.
‪Ga-yeon and Kyung-ho have that.
‪That's why they enjoy each other.
‪That was a great insight, Joo-heon.
‪-They enjoy each other's company.
‪-Yeah.
‪But Ye-rim keeps dampening the mood.
‪He said he was going to talk with you.
‪Then, I'll wait with you looking bored.
‪Glance over
‪-and try to make eye contact.
‪-Okay.
‪-Good.
‪-Who wants to see the Big Dipper outside?
‪-Me.
‪Let's go.
‪I found the Big Dipper.
‪-You did?
‪-Yeah.
‪Is it visible right now?
‪It was right here.
‪I found it.
‪-You found it?
‪-It's right there.
‪-Right?
‪-Yeah.
‪What is this?
‪I don't know.
‪Are you getting sick of this?
‪No, I'm not.
‪-I really don't know.
‪-I'm sorry.
‪You don't have to apologize.
‪Didn't it feel like
‪he was deliberately avoiding me?
‪-He may be doing it deliberately.
‪-Yeah.
‪He hasn't made eye contact with me at all.
‪Oops.
‪Why is she making that sad face?
‪This is her the whole time.
‪Gosh. You know,
‪I'm watching with a heavy heart
‪because she's like my past self.
‪It's so deflating.
‪Be confident. Please!
‪When your feelings aren't reciprocated,
‪you end up reading too much
‪into that person
‪and painting them as the bad person.
‪It’s embarrassing
‪because I see so much of myself in her.
‪It's hard for me even now.
‪Moments ago, your Heart Chip votes
‪crowned the third king.
‪Please congratulate them
‪with a round of applause.
‪We aren't checking the results?
‪Will they tell us tomorrow?
‪The third king is…
‪All right, Jung-min.
‪Let's go, Jung-min.
‪The third king is
‪Park Do-geon.
‪It's Park Do-geon.
‪-But she put in one. What?
‪-How?
‪I don't understand.
‪Chae-rin only gave one.
‪Wait.
‪Wait. I'm getting scared.
‪What did Ye-rim do?
‪The third king is
‪Park Do-geon.
‪It's Park Do-geon.
‪How?
‪We combined the total of the Heart Chips
‪and Black Heart Chips,
‪and Park Do-geon has become
‪the third king.
‪How did Do-geon…
‪-No way! Ye-rim?
‪-Ye-rim looked at him
‪and nodded.
‪EARLIER, DURING THE HEART CHIP VOTE
‪PARK DO-GEON, GONGGI
‪She put all of it in?
‪Did Ye-rim put all of it in?
‪I gave almost all of mine to Do-geon.
‪The only tactic I can use now
‪is making you king.
‪SHE PLOTTED TO MAKE DO-GEON KING
‪I'm going to make Do-geon king.
‪Are you going to vote for Do-geon too?
‪-Yeah, I can do that.
‪-Yeah?
‪If you have the black ones, exchange them
‪and give them to Ga-yeon and Kyung-ho.
‪HA-YOON PUT 25 BLACK HEARTS EACH
‪TO GA-YEON AND KYUNG-HO
‪HYE-WON GAVE HEARTS TO DO-GEON TOO
‪We'll all make you king.
‪If Kyung-ho or Ga-yeon became king,
‪they would likely choose each other.
‪I have to go on
‪the final date with Kyung-ho.
‪That's why I put so many Heart Chips
‪into Do-geon's box.
‪YE-RIM GAVE DO-GEON
‪205 HEARTS
‪PARK DO-GEON: 205 FROM YE-RIM
‪1 FROM CHAE-RIN, 26 FROM HYE-WON
‪PARK DO-GEON
‪232 HEARTS
‪I finally got the power.
‪I got goosebumps.
‪Dynamite can come in small packages.
‪You're the substitute king.
‪I'm the real king.
‪Did he have to put it that way?
‪He was being sarcastic. "Substitute king."
‪-I left a little and put most in yours.
‪-Really?
‪Were the feelings bigger than you thought?
‪Maybe he's high on himself doing that.
‪They act like they are
‪the only two people in the world.
‪It's annoying?
‪Man, things are going to blow up today.
‪It was such a headache.
‪I was jealous, but I didn't think
‪she would change her mind.
‪The way you express how you feel
‪is so different from how Jung-min does it.
‪Come to me.
‪Let's begin the game.
‪The rules of Love Marble.
‪I'd like to know
‪who Ga-yeon's first choice is.
‪What do I do?
‪What is the right thing to do?
‪Subtitle translation by: Ilyoung Kim
‪THE LOVE LAB